/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60361f310c817f0398fa1589"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-web-development-as-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "“Machine Learning is Overrated and Web Development is Underrated” Yes, This is no doubt a very bitter truth for many but This is one of the best advice I got from someone who recently got placed at Amazon i.e. my own Cousin. She said Everyone loves Word Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence even in their first year but The Truth is Machine Learning is very rarely used or used in very high-level projects. The Freshers or even SDE Jobs first are for Development only and Mostly have to work on the Web Development as ranging from Even Small Startup to Tech Giants like Amazon surely have their website. Let me show you something: -  Source 2: -  The above Source is from One of the Best Websites known for their NanoDegree Programmers. Yes, You guessed it right that is Udacity only. You can even r Continue Reading “Machine Learning is Overrated and Web Development is Underrated” Yes, This is no doubt a very bitter truth for many but This is one of the best advice I got from someone who recently got placed at Amazon i.e. my own Cousin. She said Everyone loves Word Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence even in their first year but The Truth is Machine Learning is very rarely used or used in very high-level projects. The Freshers or even SDE Jobs first are for Development only and Mostly have to work on the Web Development as ranging from Even Small Startup to Tech Giants like Amazon surely have their website. Let me show you something: -  Source 2: -  The above Source is from One of the Best Websites known for their NanoDegree Programmers. Yes, You guessed it right that is Udacity only. You can even r Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:41:05.364Z"),
    "question" : "How good is web development as a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60361f410c817f0398fa15c1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-career-advice-for-a-software-developer-to-earn-a-higher-salary?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the best career advice for a software developer to earn a higher salary?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:41:21.973Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best career advice for a software developer to earn a higher salary? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60361f6a0c817f0398fa15cd"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-a-career-in-digital-marketing?-",
    "answer" : "Saurabh Mhase I have been working in the Digital Marketing domain for the past 6 years. A career in this domain is very much rewarding if you are willing to go an extra mile. I am also mentioning the salaries towards the end of the post. However, I would like to go into specifics and explain what makes you a very good Digital marketer? The zeal for learning: The digital marketing world is very dynamic. Google itself makes over 500 changes per year in its algorithm. Facebook keeps on adding new ad formats to their ad network. You need to be aware of this. There are new mediums, tools coming in each month, you need to try these to have an upper hand in your area of expertise.Creativity: Creativity is very important. As you need to evaluate videos, creatives for the campaigns. Creative copywriting is an esseContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:42:02.292Z"),
    "question" : "How good is a career in digital marketing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60361fba0c817f0398fa1654"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-the-career-look-like-for-a-Salesforce-Developer?-",
    "answer" : "Work with a world-overwhelming innovation Salesforce is the world's driving CRM stage. It's posted a normal year-on-year development of 25% for as long as four years and has goal-oriented designs to twofold its development throughout the following four. Furthermore, a significant piece of that development will be the production of new Salesforce positions—an expected 3.3 million new openings by 2022, to be accurate. As computerized change keeps on moving over the world, leaving no industry immaculate, the interest for cloud experts is set to soar, and those with involvement with building up the world's most famous CRM will be enormously searched after. Appreciate broad openings for work Interest for Salesforce experts is progressively quickly; unmistakably more rapidly than the labor force can  Continue Reading Work with a world-overwhelming innovation Salesforce is the world's driving CRM stage. It's posted a normal year-on-year development of 25% for as long as four years and has goal-oriented designs to twofold its development throughout the following four. Furthermore, a significant piece of that development will be the production of new Salesforce positions—an expected 3.3 million new openings by 2022, to be accurate. As computerized change keeps on moving over the world, leaving no industry immaculate, the interest for cloud experts is set to soar, and those with involvement with building up the world's most famous CRM will be enormously searched after. Appreciate broad openings for work Interest for Salesforce experts is progressively quickly; unmistakably more rapidly than the labor force can  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:43:22.931Z"),
    "question" : "How does the career look like for a Salesforce Developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60361fcf0c817f0398fa1663"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-path-of-a-front-end-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the career path of a front-end developer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:43:43.791Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career path of a front-end developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60361fe40c817f0398fa166b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-Pie-Infocomm-for-starting-a-career-as-a-software-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How is Pie Infocomm for starting a career as a software developer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:44:04.061Z"),
    "question" : "How is Pie Infocomm for starting a career as a software developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036200e0c817f0398fa16ae"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-web-development-a-dying-career?-",
    "answer" : "Nicholas Hargreaves I think one of the reasons why this question is frequently asked is because getting a website has become much easier and cheaper nowadays (especially with WordPress). Anyone with a computer and an internet connection can start a website or an online business, even without being technically literate. There are templates available online, and there’s also purchasable websites at affordable prices. So, is web development dying as a career? We could perhaps say that web development as it used to be, is dead; but from another point of view we can look at it as this: Web development is changing. Sure, it’s not how it was before. Technologies are changing, and so is the need for developers who have expertise in these new technologies. There is now a need for development teams for web and mobile devel Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:44:46.726Z"),
    "question" : "Is web development a dying career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603620330c817f0398fa16ef"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-game-development-as-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "I completely agree with David Mullich‘s reply, and would like to add a few more points that tell you how a career would be in GameDev: 1- It requires patience, flexibility, and perseverance: Let’s broadly term gaming as “interactive entertainment.” This is something hard to sell to people - and the consumer behavior changes according to multiple factors. Let’s call this “the business side of game dev”. You have to be fully aware that these factors shaping consumer behavior trickle down to each individual working in game dev through planning, scheduling, financial situation of the company you work for as well as its stakeholders/partners. If you’re not flexible (through an understanding that even most LARGE companies doing game dev NEED to be flexible due to these market factors) in your min Continue Reading I completely agree with David Mullich‘s reply, and would like to add a few more points that tell you how a career would be in GameDev: 1- It requires patience, flexibility, and perseverance: Let’s broadly term gaming as “interactive entertainment.” This is something hard to sell to people - and the consumer behavior changes according to multiple factors. Let’s call this “the business side of game dev”. You have to be fully aware that these factors shaping consumer behavior trickle down to each individual working in game dev through planning, scheduling, financial situation of the company you work for as well as its stakeholders/partners. If you’re not flexible (through an understanding that even most LARGE companies doing game dev NEED to be flexible due to these market factors) in your min Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:45:23.114Z"),
    "question" : "How is game development as a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603620460c817f0398fa16fb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-start-a-career-in-International-Development?-",
    "answer" : "Makarand Sahasrabuddhe Some interesting answers and links to blogs have come up already. I am answering based on my experience. I started my work in India and moved to a different location 14 years later.  The options and routes differ depending on whether you belonging to the 'developing world' or the 'donor world' - nothing correct or incorrect about it; just the way it is. As far as entry is concerned   If you are from the developed world that is home to International NGOs and / or bilateral donor agencies, it is much easier to get in even at a very young age. Even a college degree in a related field - economics, politics, law, sociology, development is more often adequate to get in. If you are from the developing world, it is much more difficult. The biggest difficulty is the entry barrier. This is NOT deliberatContinue Reading Some interesting answers and links to blogs have come up already. I am answering based on my experience. I started my work in India and moved to a different location 14 years later.  The options and routes differ depending on whether you belonging to the 'developing world' or the 'donor world' - nothing correct or incorrect about it; just the way it is. As far as entry is concerned   If you are from the developed world that is home to International NGOs and / or bilateral donor agencies, it is much easier to get in even at a very young age. Even a college degree in a related field - economics, politics, law, sociology, development is more often adequate to get in. If you are from the developing world, it is much more difficult. The biggest difficulty is the entry barrier. This is NOT deliberatContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:45:42.965Z"),
    "question" : "How can I start a career in International Development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036205a0c817f0398fa1705"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-software-development-a-good-career?-",
    "answer" : "Not at all. Probably, 20 years ago it was good career but nowadays situation changed. The reasons: 1. Low wages: Yes there are some extra talented experts who earn probably 250-300K $ working at Google or Amazon but generally they are outliers. Majority SE earns less than 100K $ or even 50K $ in US. In comparison to medical doctors where even the worst doctor earn starting from 200K $ and the bests probably more than million dollars. 2. You need continuously update your knowledge: Languages, frameworks, paradigms etc. changes literally everyday. If you don't learn something new you become fall behind form other fellows. It will affect to your salary soon. 3. Too many newcomers nowadays and globalization: In the time of online moocs, bootcamps, the events like \"Become Python developer in 5 week\" Continue Reading Continue Reading Abhinav Jagetia",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:46:02.867Z"),
    "question" : "Is software development a good career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603620a80c817f0398fa1786"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-makes-web-development-so-difficult-to-learn?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What makes web development so difficult to learn?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:47:20.042Z"),
    "question" : "What makes web development so difficult to learn? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603620ca0c817f0398fa1791"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Are-web-development-jobs-stable?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Are web development jobs stable?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:47:54.702Z"),
    "question" : "Are web development jobs stable? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603620e00c817f0398fa17d0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-have-a-successful-career?-",
    "answer" : "Right after you pass out tenth standard, you should have a clear idea or at least have an idea as to what your strengths and weaknesses are. I know it's difficult to assess at that age. But to be more successful it's important to know what exactly you want at that age. It will pave the way to build a strong Base for your career. I agree it's the duty of the schools to let know the child as to what he or she can become with the amount of inclination at that particular age. But sadly our schools are unable to do that. And even parents are unable to guide their children, despite their so called education. Career counselling as a profession is not that sought after in a country like India. But with the Advent of Internet it has become easy for all of us to get exposed to a new world where a fift Continue Reading Right after you pass out tenth standard, you should have a clear idea or at least have an idea as to what your strengths and weaknesses are. I know it's difficult to assess at that age. But to be more successful it's important to know what exactly you want at that age. It will pave the way to build a strong Base for your career. I agree it's the duty of the schools to let know the child as to what he or she can become with the amount of inclination at that particular age. But sadly our schools are unable to do that. And even parents are unable to guide their children, despite their so called education. Career counselling as a profession is not that sought after in a country like India. But with the Advent of Internet it has become easy for all of us to get exposed to a new world where a fift Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:48:16.423Z"),
    "question" : "How can I have a successful career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603621050c817f0398fa17db"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-build-my-career-as-a-JavaScript-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How can I build my career as a JavaScript developer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:48:53.743Z"),
    "question" : "How can I build my career as a JavaScript developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036211c0c817f0398fa181a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-programming-languages-should-I-learn-for-web-development?-My-goal-is-to-build-a-text-based-game-online.-I-have-never-coded-before.-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What programming languages should I learn for web development? My goal is to build a text based game online. I have never coded before.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:49:16.127Z"),
    "question" : "What programming languages should I learn for web development? My goal is to build a text based game online. I have never coded before. ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603621300c817f0398fa1820"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-jobs-to-sign-up-for-web-development?-",
    "answer" : "It all depends on your skillset. There are following options in the web development itself: UX DeveloperUI DeveloperApplication DeveloperUX Developers combine their research and design skills together to understand the user needs and produce concepts/solutions/designs that people want to use. This requires a focus on human behaviours, psychology and understanding why people do what they do. It’s all the soft squishy, creative stuff on the right-side of the brain.  Most UXers can tell you what it should do and why it should do it, but can’t actually build something that works. UI Developers fill the middle ground by combining both design sensibilities and technical skills together. They are skilled at making something both look good and function in a browser/device at the same time. They ha Continue Reading It all depends on your skillset. There are following options in the web development itself: UX DeveloperUI DeveloperApplication DeveloperUX Developers combine their research and design skills together to understand the user needs and produce concepts/solutions/designs that people want to use. This requires a focus on human behaviours, psychology and understanding why people do what they do. It’s all the soft squishy, creative stuff on the right-side of the brain.  Most UXers can tell you what it should do and why it should do it, but can’t actually build something that works. UI Developers fill the middle ground by combining both design sensibilities and technical skills together. They are skilled at making something both look good and function in a browser/device at the same time. They ha Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:49:36.345Z"),
    "question" : "What are jobs to sign up for web development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603621460c817f0398fa1828"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-machine-learning-and-deep-learning-a-better-career-than-web-development-now?-",
    "answer" : "Lalit Patel One car salesman said that the convertible in front of the dealership sells the station wagon in the back. In my view that’s the same with ML and “regular” development. At my job I’m supposed to do Machine learning, Data mining and Artificial Intelligence. In reality, I’m doing databases (in range of 10–20 GB) and interact with idiots who believe that what I do is Data Science and Big Data. Obviously, on the slow and overpriced Amazon hardware, everything looks like big data. My advantage is that I can write any application from a large ERP to a microcontroller program. Also, I can effectively manage teams of programmers, plus I hold a PhD in computer science. This is the case in the whole industry. People don’t understand Machine Learning. Sometimes I am asked to write neural networks that a Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:49:58.311Z"),
    "question" : "Is machine learning and deep learning a better career than web development now? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036215a0c817f0398fa1867"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-of-Front-End-Developers?-",
    "answer" : "Here’s the thing. I don’t consider myself a front end developer, despite the fact that I write a huge amount of front end applications. I also don’t count myself a back end developer, despite having built some very complex back end systems. I count myself a developer, so I don’t have limitations on what I work on. Why do I say this? There are some potential “paradigm shifts” coming through that are of particular interest that may end up having quite an impact on the way we write applications, and the targets that our applications have. Apologies, in advance, for what might become a very rambling post. I see, from some of the answers here, that people are obsessing on web applications as the be-all and end-all of front end development. What is interesting is that we are seeing a movement away Continue Reading Here’s the thing. I don’t consider myself a front end developer, despite the fact that I write a huge amount of front end applications. I also don’t count myself a back end developer, despite having built some very complex back end systems. I count myself a developer, so I don’t have limitations on what I work on. Why do I say this? There are some potential “paradigm shifts” coming through that are of particular interest that may end up having quite an impact on the way we write applications, and the targets that our applications have. Apologies, in advance, for what might become a very rambling post. I see, from some of the answers here, that people are obsessing on web applications as the be-all and end-all of front end development. What is interesting is that we are seeing a movement away Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:50:18.642Z"),
    "question" : "What is the future of Front End Developers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036216c0c817f0398fa1871"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-front-end-web-development-a-good-career-today?-",
    "answer" : "Geoffrey Ok Front end development is a great career in 2017, but don’t get hit by the bus. There is all the hype around as to which is the latest cool front end technology to learn as a beginner. You assign yourself a task to learn front end development only to realize that the task is to find the particular framework to learn. Let me give you a few tips that will help you be a better front end developer. 1. Learn JavaScript It’s great that you have already mentioned that you know some jQuery. That is great, though you should know that jQuery is not JavaScript. In fact, front end developer is another name for a JavaScript developer. JavaScript is the programming language that you will use throughout your front end development. Forget about CoffeeScript for now. 2. Build some Boostrap themes It is quite easy to Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:50:36.696Z"),
    "question" : "Is front end web development a good career today? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603621920c817f0398fa18b4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-get-a-job-as-a-python-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Source: Python Career Opportunities 101: Your Guide To A Career In Python Programming Python is a premier, flexible, and powerful open-source language that is easy to learn, easy to use, and has powerful libraries for data manipulation and analysis. With the popularity of Python programming language moving steadily along an upward trajectory, the time is right to master Python in order to land Python jobs. In this bog post, we will discuss various Python career opportunities available for a Python programmer. Python Career Opportunities In an independent third party survey, it has been revealed that the Python programming language is currently the most popular language for data scientists worldwide.This claim is substantiated by the Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers, which tracContinue Reading Source: Python Career Opportunities 101: Your Guide To A Career In Python Programming Python is a premier, flexible, and powerful open-source language that is easy to learn, easy to use, and has powerful libraries for data manipulation and analysis. With the popularity of Python programming language moving steadily along an upward trajectory, the time is right to master Python in order to land Python jobs. In this bog post, we will discuss various Python career opportunities available for a Python programmer. Python Career Opportunities In an independent third party survey, it has been revealed that the Python programming language is currently the most popular language for data scientists worldwide.This claim is substantiated by the Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers, which tracContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:51:14.926Z"),
    "question" : "How do I get a job as a python developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603621a80c817f0398fa18bb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-30-really-too-old-to-start-a-career-as-a-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Is 30 really too old to start a career as a developer? Nope. (Going anonymous here because my case is pretty specific and I'm just starting my new job). I'm a bit younger, mid-twenties. I have an advanced degree in a biological science. I began teaching myself to code a little over a year ago with very rudimentary HTML code. When I started, I hadn't coded since high school either. It didn't matter, I had only done HTML then and didn't remember much of it if any at all. It was hard. Really hard. The HTML and CSS classes I found online were straightforward and I finished them quickly. But once I tried to create a simple webpage on my own or recreate something without help, I was lost. But I just kept at it and eventually it all started to make some sense. I moved on to JavaScript, which was absolutely mind-blowing. I had never seen it before, the  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:51:36.078Z"),
    "question" : "Is 30 really too old to start a career as a developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603621cd0c817f0398fa18fd"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-of-the-career-option-is-better-full-stack-developer-or-data-scientist?-",
    "answer" : "Your job as a full stack developer must have already given you the knowledge and base of Databases, system engineering, servers, web applications, etc. And Data science is purely related to deriving meaning out of your existing data in order to move towards predictive analysis and use it for businesses to make the right and informed decisions. Truth be told, it completely depends upon your inclination towards either of the subjects. But here are a few facts that might help you make the right decision for shaping your future. Considering the current times of advanced technologies, you must have a heard a lot about the Artificial Intelligence, machine learning, data visualizations and many similar terms, which are preceding every other field now. With this exponential popularity, data sciences an Continue Reading Your job as a full stack developer must have already given you the knowledge and base of Databases, system engineering, servers, web applications, etc. And Data science is purely related to deriving meaning out of your existing data in order to move towards predictive analysis and use it for businesses to make the right and informed decisions. Truth be told, it completely depends upon your inclination towards either of the subjects. But here are a few facts that might help you make the right decision for shaping your future. Considering the current times of advanced technologies, you must have a heard a lot about the Artificial Intelligence, machine learning, data visualizations and many similar terms, which are preceding every other field now. With this exponential popularity, data sciences an Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:52:13.460Z"),
    "question" : "Which of the career option is better full stack developer or data scientist? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603621e10c817f0398fa1903"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-prospects-for-an-Android-application-developer?-Whom-do-they-work-for?-",
    "answer" : "The Android OS is literally flexing its muscles in the mobile domain and it won’t be wrong to say that jobs for Android application development might any day surpass horizon to being the most demanded and sought after operating system. The Android applications platform promises a vast job potential in the field of IT. With the onslaught of robust usage of android devices, Android is not just confined to being application development. It has scope in hardware solutions too, such as customization an optimization of android devices and drivers.The job market of Android is gaining an amazing momentum. There is a dearth of talent in the Android field. Very soon, in the near future, major companies will make a line seeking for good Android development professionals. So, for those who are planni Continue Reading The Android OS is literally flexing its muscles in the mobile domain and it won’t be wrong to say that jobs for Android application development might any day surpass horizon to being the most demanded and sought after operating system. The Android applications platform promises a vast job potential in the field of IT. With the onslaught of robust usage of android devices, Android is not just confined to being application development. It has scope in hardware solutions too, such as customization an optimization of android devices and drivers.The job market of Android is gaining an amazing momentum. There is a dearth of talent in the Android field. Very soon, in the near future, major companies will make a line seeking for good Android development professionals. So, for those who are planni Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:52:33.980Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career prospects for an Android application developer? Whom do they work for? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603622160c817f0398fa194b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-will-the-career-be-for-a-web-developer-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Hello There! I would say it is still a great time to pursue web development as your career. Two things are never going out of fashion no matter what: 1. Visuals 2. Numerical And, both of these engineers are very much in demand. In today’s strictly competitive environment, companies are working hard to bring up their innovative products into the market. To stay very much in demand, they want continuous innovation and new product lines. We are already dependent on technology in our day to day activities. · To set alarm we use Google Assistant, Alexa, Siri, etc · We start our day with listening songs on SoundCloud, Wink, Gaana, etc. · For transporting form one place to another, we use Uber, Ola. · In our office, for work we use Google Sheets, Google Docs, Skype, Slack, Google Hangouts for talks, and  Continue Reading Hello There! I would say it is still a great time to pursue web development as your career. Two things are never going out of fashion no matter what: 1. Visuals 2. Numerical And, both of these engineers are very much in demand. In today’s strictly competitive environment, companies are working hard to bring up their innovative products into the market. To stay very much in demand, they want continuous innovation and new product lines. We are already dependent on technology in our day to day activities. · To set alarm we use Google Assistant, Alexa, Siri, etc · We start our day with listening songs on SoundCloud, Wink, Gaana, etc. · For transporting form one place to another, we use Uber, Ola. · In our office, for work we use Google Sheets, Google Docs, Skype, Slack, Google Hangouts for talks, and  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:53:26.195Z"),
    "question" : "How will the career be for a web developer in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036222c0c817f0398fa1953"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-path-of-a-web-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Let me tell you my story.I worked as a Web Developer in a small company in Bangalore, India which had like  for 1 Year 9 months. During which I drew an initial salary of 10,703 INR/month as I joined there as a fresher i.e, with no professional experience in any sort of field. For the first year, and 14,420 INR/month for the next 9 months. I worked with people who had 4+, 3+ and 2+ years of work experience which comprised of developers and themers. The guy who had 4+ years of experience in the same company from start, drew a salary of around 50K+ INR/month or more I guess, this is a pretty less salary for a guy who has 4+ years of experience and who was pretty good at what he does. He could find answers to almost all the problems we faced while we did our assigned tasks if at all we couldn' Continue Reading Let me tell you my story.I worked as a Web Developer in a small company in Bangalore, India which had like  for 1 Year 9 months. During which I drew an initial salary of 10,703 INR/month as I joined there as a fresher i.e, with no professional experience in any sort of field. For the first year, and 14,420 INR/month for the next 9 months. I worked with people who had 4+, 3+ and 2+ years of work experience which comprised of developers and themers. The guy who had 4+ years of experience in the same company from start, drew a salary of around 50K+ INR/month or more I guess, this is a pretty less salary for a guy who has 4+ years of experience and who was pretty good at what he does. He could find answers to almost all the problems we faced while we did our assigned tasks if at all we couldn' Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:53:48.679Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career path of a web developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603622430c817f0398fa1991"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Web-development-a-dying-career-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Tejaswi Bitra, An ex freelancer. Used to make websites for a living.Answered 3 years ago · Author has 1.1K answers and 1.7M answer viewsIs Web development a dying career in India? Tejaswi Bitra “Being a 2014 pass out B.E(ECE) and learning Web dev now,will it really help me get a job(as there are better people who have developed many projects) or is there any short term course which would help me get a job? I learnt Java earlier but no job. “ I understand your feeling. I was there. I understand your frustration. But, just because you have learned JAVA, that does not guarantee a job. There may be lacks of graduates clearing exams every year who are decent with JAVA. what makes you stand out? why should recruiters choose you? Give them that reason. Be different.  How to be different? A few tips which may work(remember, there are no guarantees): Create projects which catch people’s eye. Since you are a JAVA guy, build a web service which helps to solve a particular problem for a person/orgContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:54:11.405Z"),
    "question" : "Is Web development a dying career in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603622570c817f0398fa1997"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-scopes-of-Web-development-jobs?-",
    "answer" : "The demand for web developers is huge, and it’s not going anywhere unless someone shuts down the internet. But being a broad domain, you should be particular about the job role you want to build your career around. Here are the most in-demand job roles for making career in the field of web development— Front End DeveloperA front end developer handles the visual aspect, the final version that users see on a website i.e. the client-side interface.The average salary for an entry-level front end developer in India is 4 Lacs per annum. Add some years of work experience to that and the numbers reach to a minimum of 6–8 Lacs per annum.IT giants like Flipkart, Paytm, Zomato, Ola, Uber etc actively hire for front end positions, along with other companies and startups and are willing to pay some handsContinue Reading The demand for web developers is huge, and it’s not going anywhere unless someone shuts down the internet. But being a broad domain, you should be particular about the job role you want to build your career around. Here are the most in-demand job roles for making career in the field of web development— Front End DeveloperA front end developer handles the visual aspect, the final version that users see on a website i.e. the client-side interface.The average salary for an entry-level front end developer in India is 4 Lacs per annum. Add some years of work experience to that and the numbers reach to a minimum of 6–8 Lacs per annum.IT giants like Flipkart, Paytm, Zomato, Ola, Uber etc actively hire for front end positions, along with other companies and startups and are willing to pay some handsContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:54:31.196Z"),
    "question" : "What are the scopes of Web development jobs? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036227f0c817f0398fa19db"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-PHP-developer-a-good-career-for-fresher?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is PHP developer a good career for fresher?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:55:11.100Z"),
    "question" : "Is PHP developer a good career for fresher? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603622940c817f0398fa19e5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-game-programming-still-considered-a-great-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Konrad Krupa",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:55:32.415Z"),
    "question" : "Is game programming still considered a great career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603622aa0c817f0398fa19ed"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-get-started-with-Android-application-development-with-only-very-basic-knowledge-about-programming?-",
    "answer" : "Vyshnav Ramesh, Reached database phaseAnswered 4 years ago · Author has 235 answers and 355.3K answer viewsHow do I get started with Android application development with only very basic knowledge about programming? Vyshnav Ramesh I knew only C++ and started learning Android this Feb 1 Following are the things what I experienced during my journey: SETTING UP PHASE: 1. Maybe the most hectic part for a beginner as well as for an expert. You have to install Java (jdk and jre, both comes combined, so don't worry), and then Android Studio. Note: Avoid Eclipse. It's old. The best tutorial for setting up these is Newboston. Though the video is old, the procedure is still the same and he has the best explanation. LEARNING PHASE: 1. Video tutorials are better than blogs because written contents may get you confused. So go for youtube! 2. Make sure your tutorials/ videos are mostly from this year ie, latest, since Android Studio (the software in,which you write Android codes) has drastically been upgraded this year to version 2.1 ( Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:55:54.788Z"),
    "question" : "How do I get started with Android application development with only very basic knowledge about programming? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603622bf0c817f0398fa1a2c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-start-career-as-Java-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Deepu Singh 3 steps you should take to make a break as a Java developer: Step 1: Invest in improving your job hunting skills encompassing interviewing, networking, and resume writing skills. Step 2: Keep applying for jobs via both published & hidden job markets.[/list] Step 3: Follow the tips outlined below to enhance your hands-on experience while keeping at points 1 & 2. Getting the much needed hands-on experience Tip #1: Java is very accessible and all the following are available for free. The steps you take may slightly vary depending on your familiarity with Java and its tools. A computer -- desk top or lap top. Download latest version of Java (JDK and JRE). Download latest version of eclipse IDE. Download Tomcat or JBoss to deploy your applications. Download and install MySQL database. All non trivial app Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:56:15.341Z"),
    "question" : "How can I start career as Java developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603622e30c817f0398fa1a38"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-your-regrets-as-a-developer-at-the-end-of-your-career?-",
    "answer" : "I think you can see from most of the answers that most software developers have few regrets at the end of their career, at least if they stayed with their career for their whole life. I think the answer might be quite different for those who “burnt out” or were “forced out” and left a development career by other than retiring, but those people probably don’t consider themselves developers at the end of their career. In any case, there is a relatively simple reason for why developers have few regrets at the end of their career. They chose to end their career. And, of course, that’s why people who burnt out or were forced out before the end might have a different answer. One can use my career as an example. I am on the borderline between the two situations. A little over a year ago I retired. F Continue Reading I think you can see from most of the answers that most software developers have few regrets at the end of their career, at least if they stayed with their career for their whole life. I think the answer might be quite different for those who “burnt out” or were “forced out” and left a development career by other than retiring, but those people probably don’t consider themselves developers at the end of their career. In any case, there is a relatively simple reason for why developers have few regrets at the end of their career. They chose to end their career. And, of course, that’s why people who burnt out or were forced out before the end might have a different answer. One can use my career as an example. I am on the borderline between the two situations. A little over a year ago I retired. F Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:56:51.610Z"),
    "question" : "What are your regrets as a developer at the end of your career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603622fa0c817f0398fa1a76"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-becoming-an-Android-Developer-a-good-option?-",
    "answer" : "It definitely is a good career opportunity.. You very well know.. majorly ANDROID AND IOS have taken market these days… and most people make use of Android smartphones as it is quite affordable for middle class and obviously for upper classes making it most demanded technology… Everyday millions of and you sure know how fast different Versions of Android Technology has evolved in recent times… SO THAT MEANS THERE IS DEMAND FOR IT… and every single business/product in the world are launching their Android apps..every day millions of such apps are developed worldwide !!.. So like I said there is demand giving rise to scope for developers to show their skills.. Again YOU CAN EITHER JOIN ANY REPUTED COMPANY AS AN ANDROID DEVELOPER ..AND YOU MIGHT GET A SALRY OF 15K INR STARTING OUT !! .. as well Continue Reading It definitely is a good career opportunity.. You very well know.. majorly ANDROID AND IOS have taken market these days… and most people make use of Android smartphones as it is quite affordable for middle class and obviously for upper classes making it most demanded technology… Everyday millions of and you sure know how fast different Versions of Android Technology has evolved in recent times… SO THAT MEANS THERE IS DEMAND FOR IT… and every single business/product in the world are launching their Android apps..every day millions of such apps are developed worldwide !!.. So like I said there is demand giving rise to scope for developers to show their skills.. Again YOU CAN EITHER JOIN ANY REPUTED COMPANY AS AN ANDROID DEVELOPER ..AND YOU MIGHT GET A SALRY OF 15K INR STARTING OUT !! .. as well Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:57:14.091Z"),
    "question" : "Is becoming an Android Developer a good option? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036232d0c817f0398fa1a87"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-you-design-a-career-plan-for-yourself?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do you design a career plan for yourself?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:58:05.631Z"),
    "question" : "How do you design a career plan for yourself? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603623440c817f0398fa1ac3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-has-helped-you-the-most-in-advancing-your-software-development-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What has helped you the most in advancing your software development career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:58:28.684Z"),
    "question" : "What has helped you the most in advancing your software development career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036236a0c817f0398fa1ad1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-developing-careers-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "e-commerce and cut throat competition in tele data are the developing careers . the two branches need software professionals in coding, digitalisation, cloud computing, data management and similar fields now, banking digitalisation and gateways , retails, mobile applications are also looking in for it professionals",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:59:06.434Z"),
    "question" : "What are the developing careers in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603623910c817f0398fa1b13"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-downsides-to-a-career-in-software-development?-",
    "answer" : "The career has some similarities to the career of a professional athlete - it is very difficult to stay in the role for your entire career. There are multiple reasons which are subtle and are not anything as simple as “older people can’t keep up” (absolutely not true). Closer to the truth is that the industry really doesn’t have that many projects and leadership roles in teams that are creating the grand, new “something” from a blank sheet of paper. Rather, the vast majority of the activity is bug fixes, and small tweaks to big blobs of legacy code. Most managers who are hiring for these roles would rather hire younger people who are still learning. Although this attitude is frustrating if you are an older person applying for the job, the attitude is not “evil”. Rather, if you are a manager  Continue Reading The career has some similarities to the career of a professional athlete - it is very difficult to stay in the role for your entire career. There are multiple reasons which are subtle and are not anything as simple as “older people can’t keep up” (absolutely not true). Closer to the truth is that the industry really doesn’t have that many projects and leadership roles in teams that are creating the grand, new “something” from a blank sheet of paper. Rather, the vast majority of the activity is bug fixes, and small tweaks to big blobs of legacy code. Most managers who are hiring for these roles would rather hire younger people who are still learning. Although this attitude is frustrating if you are an older person applying for the job, the attitude is not “evil”. Rather, if you are a manager  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T09:59:45.891Z"),
    "question" : "What are the downsides to a career in software development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603623a40c817f0398fa1b1a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-develop-my-career-as-a-web-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Amit Shekhar Your negotiation skills matter: Well, this is quite a generic and applicable to all the fields, but yes, how you negotiate matters a lot. You may end up at 12LPA CTC but if you are effective in negotiating, you can push your salary to 15 LPA. Outsource your codes: Life is too short to code everything by yourself. Study codes, understand codes and implement codes from open platforms. StackOverflow is an amazing temple of codes. Visit such temples and get blessings. Softskills matter: Excuse me! I have read this before. If you just had this thought then well yes, it does matter and reading \"soft skills matter\" now or before does not matter. It is an art that needs crafting and you gotta work on it. It is not about faking communication, it is about being sane enough to talk effectively. All tha Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:00:04.268Z"),
    "question" : "How can I develop my career as a web developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603623b80c817f0398fa1b56"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-of-your-best-pieces-of-advice-for-career-development?-",
    "answer" : "Rafael Sarandeses I can summarise it as “You can only connect the dots backwards.” (Steve Jobs). Let me explain what I mean by this: 1. Change your idea of what “making an impact” means I see young people nowadays starting their careers with a lot of enthusiasm, just to become bored and disappointed after a few months, the most common feedback being “I am not making an impact”. But as my ex-colleague at Goldman Sachs Joseph Mauro famously said one day, you have to “stay on the bus”. We can make an impact every day with tiny things, but we tend to discard this as valuable because we reject simple stuff in favour of complex matters. This is also applicable to how we feel. Simple is boring and not sophisticated, and you and I are fun and sophisticated people, correct? Well, you don’t need to feel “sophisticated” a Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:00:24.163Z"),
    "question" : "What are some of your best pieces of advice for career development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603623cf0c817f0398fa1b63"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-main-tips-to-start-a-web-development-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the main tips to start a web development career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:00:47.254Z"),
    "question" : "What are the main tips to start a web development career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603624210c817f0398fa1bb3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-pursue-back-end-or-front-end-development?-",
    "answer" : "A good question would be why not both? Now that you have decided to study programming, it’s a good decision but I would suggest always opt to be “out of the box guy” Backend, frontend, and full stack development are three separate career paths but if you manage to grasp them, you will be exceptional. Have you asked yourself, \"Do I enjoy making mock-ups come to life?\" and answered yes? You probably want to pursue a front end career. If you find yourself asking \"How can I use this algorithm to make an informed decision,\" you're likely a backend brain. There are many career path similarities between frontend and backend development including similar salaries, career longevity and job growth over the past five years. Back end development is aptly named for developers who deal with the back end o Continue Reading A good question would be why not both? Now that you have decided to study programming, it’s a good decision but I would suggest always opt to be “out of the box guy” Backend, frontend, and full stack development are three separate career paths but if you manage to grasp them, you will be exceptional. Have you asked yourself, \"Do I enjoy making mock-ups come to life?\" and answered yes? You probably want to pursue a front end career. If you find yourself asking \"How can I use this algorithm to make an informed decision,\" you're likely a backend brain. There are many career path similarities between frontend and backend development including similar salaries, career longevity and job growth over the past five years. Back end development is aptly named for developers who deal with the back end o Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:02:09.203Z"),
    "question" : "Should I pursue back-end or front-end development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603624370c817f0398fa1bed"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-web-developing-a-promising-career-for-the-future?-",
    "answer" : "Web development could be promising if you are willing to put in the hard work to become better than a mediocre developer. There are enough mediocre developers doing mediocre jobs with not much enthusiasm to improve their skills. If you rise above this crowd then definitely you will never go jobless.  On the other hand, one should think about a bit more than just to keep a job and getting by. Try to take calculated risk to do meaningful work. The day you retire, you should feel that the journey was worth it. Toni Alatalo",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:02:31.301Z"),
    "question" : "Is web developing a promising career for the future? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603624640c817f0398fa1c33"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-typical-career-paths-for-Python-Developers?-",
    "answer" : "At high level you can become either of: DevOpsFull Stack Developer {If you pick up Mobile Application}Web Application Developer {In frontend role}Let me tell you a story about Yogesh, Prasen and Hardik {from left to right}, they are my team leads and have been working with me for 7+ years now. When they started they didn’t have knowledge about any programming language.  Yogesh - DevOps Team Lead He has a Diploma in Chemical EngineeringInitial years he took on Sys-Admin role, when there are no networking or hardware issues he picked up Python and Shell ScriptingHe has now handled 3 Django/Python projects, including 2 migration projectsPrasen - Mobile Application Team Lead He and Hardik have BScIT DegreeHe is a full stack developer. Amongst other things he has coded projects in Node.js, ObjectiveContinue Reading At high level you can become either of: DevOpsFull Stack Developer {If you pick up Mobile Application}Web Application Developer {In frontend role}Let me tell you a story about Yogesh, Prasen and Hardik {from left to right}, they are my team leads and have been working with me for 7+ years now. When they started they didn’t have knowledge about any programming language.  Yogesh - DevOps Team Lead He has a Diploma in Chemical EngineeringInitial years he took on Sys-Admin role, when there are no networking or hardware issues he picked up Python and Shell ScriptingHe has now handled 3 Django/Python projects, including 2 migration projectsPrasen - Mobile Application Team Lead He and Hardik have BScIT DegreeHe is a full stack developer. Amongst other things he has coded projects in Node.js, ObjectiveContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:03:16.095Z"),
    "question" : "What are typical career paths for Python Developers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036248e0c817f0398fa1c3f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-Informatica-for-starting-a-career-as-Software-Developer?-",
    "answer" : "Thanks for A2A.  I started my career as an Informatica ETL developer hope my experience may help you . I started my career in 2012 September in IBM .I was assigned to Informatica domain , that was the first time when i had heard the word called \"Informatica\" . I was trained for 2 months on ETL , data warehouse concepts and in informatica.  Currently i am working as an ETL developer and Administrator in building a data warehouse for one the top 3 Bank of India . Its bang on to start your career with Informatica or any other ETL tool for that matter. Informatica is bit peculiar besides it's competitor like Abinitio,  because it's a widely used tool and the one which is affordable by tier 3 companies compared to the costly Abinitio.  There are plenty of data warehouse projects - development , testi Continue Reading Thanks for A2A.  I started my career as an Informatica ETL developer hope my experience may help you . I started my career in 2012 September in IBM .I was assigned to Informatica domain , that was the first time when i had heard the word called \"Informatica\" . I was trained for 2 months on ETL , data warehouse concepts and in informatica.  Currently i am working as an ETL developer and Administrator in building a data warehouse for one the top 3 Bank of India . Its bang on to start your career with Informatica or any other ETL tool for that matter. Informatica is bit peculiar besides it's competitor like Abinitio,  because it's a widely used tool and the one which is affordable by tier 3 companies compared to the costly Abinitio.  There are plenty of data warehouse projects - development , testi Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:03:58.082Z"),
    "question" : "How good is Informatica for starting a career as Software Developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603624a10c817f0398fa1c7d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-way-to-develop-careers-in-game-development?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the way to develop careers in game development?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:04:17.959Z"),
    "question" : "What is the way to develop careers in game development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603625060c817f0398fa1cd3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-good-to-choose-UI-development-as-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "Sravya Sravs Yes, it is good to choose UI Development as a career. Basically choosing a career is depends on your passion and interests if you are interested in coding or the IT industry; yes web designing is a good career. Web Designing is one of the best career options to choose a profession these days. And in 2020 we have a lot of updated techniques to be a good web designer. If you are looking forward to becoming a good web designer learn updated web design trends. Basic Web Designing Programming Languages HTML/CSS Some of the highest-paid web developers are those that know HTML (Hypertext Markup Language) and CSS (Cascading Style Sheets). These are the basic languages that will not only help you know how to code but how to edit code. Typically, HTML establishes the structure and content of the page,  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:05:58.493Z"),
    "question" : "Is it good to choose UI development as a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603625180c817f0398fa1d10"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-good-to-become-a-full-stack-web-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Rasmus Frederiksen Bright based on what? Look, you’re not going to be rich from it, at least not for a long while or without so much luck you’d be famous, but neither is anyone else, except those who already have lots of money, to make even more money. But a bright career doesn’t need to revolve around money, some artists were very bright, and didn’t earn much from their paintings, they only became worth it after the artists were already dead. It’s a big learning experience, you’ll be doing at least 4 jobs in one, touching a very large span of subjects over many years.Is that bright, is that worth it?I think it is, even if I may never become rich off it. PS. yes, you can actually get a really nice pay, with about 30 years of experience, you can become a “consultant”, people respect others that they don’t know  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:06:16.440Z"),
    "question" : "Is it good to become a full stack web developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036253b0c817f0398fa1d1b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Are-Python-developers-employed-for-careers-outside-of-web-development?-",
    "answer" : "Totally, I have been coding in Python 0.0 (otherwise known as Basic), since I was 10 years old ... haha!I have found my deep knowledge of Python very useful in all kinds of statistical analysesIt has also helped me design better front-ends for stuff I build because it makes me realize the limitations of Javascript (No node js is not a back-end language to us purists- it is damn good nonethless, but I digress). And most importantly my Python knowledge makes my JS betterI also know people at big companies, like Google, and Linkedin, who manage products and have basic (no pun intended) - intermediate Python knowledge and it helps them with certain data gathering and rudimentary analyticsAlso I am repeating myself, because at the moment I am too lazy to edit my answer, lolz, with Python you cContinue Reading Totally, I have been coding in Python 0.0 (otherwise known as Basic), since I was 10 years old ... haha!I have found my deep knowledge of Python very useful in all kinds of statistical analysesIt has also helped me design better front-ends for stuff I build because it makes me realize the limitations of Javascript (No node js is not a back-end language to us purists- it is damn good nonethless, but I digress). And most importantly my Python knowledge makes my JS betterI also know people at big companies, like Google, and Linkedin, who manage products and have basic (no pun intended) - intermediate Python knowledge and it helps them with certain data gathering and rudimentary analyticsAlso I am repeating myself, because at the moment I am too lazy to edit my answer, lolz, with Python you cContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:06:51.646Z"),
    "question" : "Are Python developers employed for careers outside of web development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036254f0c817f0398fa1d59"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-career-advice-for-a-future-software-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Nicholas Hargreaves I am not a software developer, however, I do own and run an IT outsourcing company. I have spent around 20 years working with developers and I have seen countless of these talented developers grow their experience and also their pockets. There are plenty of good points and advice from this thread, but here are three major advice based on what I have seen.  Advanced Skill Set Once you’re there, there is no better way to improve your experience than to increase your skills. Master one tech language and be very good in executing it. Increasing your knowledge and experience leverage you from others and can help you get your dream project. An experienced background and knowledge on a tech language let your employer or client know that you are capable of handling more complex projects. This increas Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:07:11.946Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best career advice for a future software developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603625660c817f0398fa1d5f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-web-development-a-respectable-career?-",
    "answer" : "Not really. Everybody and their dog are getting into web development because it's perceived as a lucrative career that's easy to get into. (It's neither lucrative nor easy to get into.) Consequently, the market is flooded with new web developers who don't really know what they're doing. Web development is turning into something of a joke. Yeah, you can probably get a job as a web developer, but don't expect any respect. It's just a job, nothing more. Something like machine learning or cloud computing or IoT would impress me more. 10",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:07:34.701Z"),
    "question" : "Is web development a respectable career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036257b0c817f0398fa1d67"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Linux-Kernel-Development-still-a-good-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Sachin Mokashi",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:07:55.055Z"),
    "question" : "Is Linux Kernel Development still a good career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036258f0c817f0398fa1da6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-40-too-late-to-start-a-career-as-a-software-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is 40 too late to start a career as a software developer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:08:15.730Z"),
    "question" : "Is 40 too late to start a career as a software developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603625a40c817f0398fa1dac"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-path-to-becoming-a-game-developer?-",
    "answer" : "I'll be the devil's (major developers?) advocate here and offer a different perspective among all the answers that sing praises for indie games.  I've worked in start ups, I've also worked for and still working for major game publishers. So I could say I have experience in both worlds. If you ask me, I'd say \"indie game is not the holy grail of game development\". You can find great happiness and fulfillment in the \"gigantic soulless\" game developing/publishing companies, just like many other had done and many more still current doing, happily.  People from the outside enjoy the narrative about how big game developer/publishers are hive-minded evil commercial entities and all of their employees are brainless worker bees working on assembly lines creating identical heartless products year afte Continue Reading I'll be the devil's (major developers?) advocate here and offer a different perspective among all the answers that sing praises for indie games.  I've worked in start ups, I've also worked for and still working for major game publishers. So I could say I have experience in both worlds. If you ask me, I'd say \"indie game is not the holy grail of game development\". You can find great happiness and fulfillment in the \"gigantic soulless\" game developing/publishing companies, just like many other had done and many more still current doing, happily.  People from the outside enjoy the narrative about how big game developer/publishers are hive-minded evil commercial entities and all of their employees are brainless worker bees working on assembly lines creating identical heartless products year afte Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:08:36.689Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best path to becoming a game developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603625f60c817f0398fa1dfa"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-being-an-iOS-developer-a-good-career-choice-in-terms-of-potential-career-growth?-",
    "answer" : "Off course, I say yes. There is a lot of demand of iOS developers nowadays. Usually you get more package compare to other mobile developer. Most of rich person uses iPhone and iOS devices, so they can easily buy apps. Thats why iOS developer being paid more. In terms of development, it is easy to learn iOS programming. Mohan Babu K",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:09:58.373Z"),
    "question" : "Is being an iOS developer a good career choice in terms of potential career growth? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036260c0c817f0398fa1e38"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-Mobile-Development-as-career?-",
    "answer" : "Ravi Bhavnani Montana Braswell Adel Alzubeir",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:10:20.214Z"),
    "question" : "How good is Mobile Development as career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603626370c817f0398fa1e4c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-good-to-start-your-career-as-a-salesforce-developer?-",
    "answer" : "It’s perfectly good. Many of us think that Salesforce is meant only for experienced people. But, actually it’s not. It stands as an open platform for fresh graduates and post graduates as well. Though you are a fresher, you can go as a Salesforce developer if you have enough knowledge in certain programming languages. Actually, Salesforce development includes specific programming languages – Apex and Visualforce. They are basically similar to Java and C#. So, when you are adept in C#, Java, and .Net, then without any doubt, you can initiate your career as a Salesforce developer. Whatever is your profile, you need to keep updated on the current industrial trends and hone your skills to work well and progress. Same is the case with Salesforce career. Though you excel in coding, it’s better to  Continue Reading It’s perfectly good. Many of us think that Salesforce is meant only for experienced people. But, actually it’s not. It stands as an open platform for fresh graduates and post graduates as well. Though you are a fresher, you can go as a Salesforce developer if you have enough knowledge in certain programming languages. Actually, Salesforce development includes specific programming languages – Apex and Visualforce. They are basically similar to Java and C#. So, when you are adept in C#, Java, and .Net, then without any doubt, you can initiate your career as a Salesforce developer. Whatever is your profile, you need to keep updated on the current industrial trends and hone your skills to work well and progress. Same is the case with Salesforce career. Though you excel in coding, it’s better to  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:11:03.008Z"),
    "question" : "Is it good to start your career as a salesforce developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603626500c817f0398fa1e89"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-start-my-development-career-as-a-Java-developer-or-a-Web-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Java is a fast, secure, and reliable programming language. Most people use Java to address core Java or JSE (Java Standard Edition). Java is all around you, as it is quietly running in laptops, data centers, game consoles, scientific supercomputers, cell phones and also on the Internet or the World Wide Web.  There are many web development companies offering Internships and Jobs for Freshers in the Web development field.  To get started as a web developer, you will need to learn these programming languages:  • HTML • CSS • JavaScript • JQuery  Once you get strong with this programming language, go on exploring extra knowledge including: • Web design / UX / Photoshop • Version control (Git / GitHub) • Cross-browser compatibility • Responsive web design  Once you know this, t Continue Reading Java is a fast, secure, and reliable programming language. Most people use Java to address core Java or JSE (Java Standard Edition). Java is all around you, as it is quietly running in laptops, data centers, game consoles, scientific supercomputers, cell phones and also on the Internet or the World Wide Web.  There are many web development companies offering Internships and Jobs for Freshers in the Web development field.  To get started as a web developer, you will need to learn these programming languages:  • HTML • CSS • JavaScript • JQuery  Once you get strong with this programming language, go on exploring extra knowledge including: • Web design / UX / Photoshop • Version control (Git / GitHub) • Cross-browser compatibility • Responsive web design  Once you know this, t Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:11:28.203Z"),
    "question" : "Should I start my development career as a Java developer or a Web developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603626650c817f0398fa1e91"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-career-growth-as-a-c++-developer?-",
    "answer" : "C and C++ are one of most respected programming language , programmers who find tough to grasp its concept may say its boring etc . Seems non replaceable in Embedded , Networks , Gaming , OS and other domains in which low level minimum latency systems are required , in near future . Once you are proficient in C++ , you could learn any programming language in a fort night . I highly recommend learning it and in case of career growth , you need nothing to fear if you are good at it . Vimal Sharma",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:11:49.120Z"),
    "question" : "How is career growth as a c++ developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603626780c817f0398fa1e99"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-get-a-job-as-a-frontend-developer?-",
    "answer" : "What is front-end development? Everything on the screen with which the user interacts is called the Front-end of the system. The front end developers are the one who decides the look and feels of the website according to the users who are going to use the system. Everything with fonts and colors , and clickable elements such as buttons drop down menus, forms everything is decided by a front-end developer. .HTML, CSS, JavaScript are the popular and basic technologies for aspiring front-end developers. Front-end developers only perform front end development.What are the career options for front-end developers? Front-end developerUI/UX designerBack-end develoeperFull-stack DeveloperSkills required to be efficient in front-end development: One should have excellent knowledge of all the necessary Continue Reading What is front-end development? Everything on the screen with which the user interacts is called the Front-end of the system. The front end developers are the one who decides the look and feels of the website according to the users who are going to use the system. Everything with fonts and colors , and clickable elements such as buttons drop down menus, forms everything is decided by a front-end developer. .HTML, CSS, JavaScript are the popular and basic technologies for aspiring front-end developers. Front-end developers only perform front end development.What are the career options for front-end developers? Front-end developerUI/UX designerBack-end develoeperFull-stack DeveloperSkills required to be efficient in front-end development: One should have excellent knowledge of all the necessary Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:12:08.199Z"),
    "question" : "How do I get a job as a frontend developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036268b0c817f0398fa1ed5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-career-growth-and-salary-hike-for-an-Informatica-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Xitiz Pugalia Hi,   The following points related to my personal experience might answer your question to some extent:- With 3 years of overall experience in the industry (after completing Bachelors in IT in the year 2012), I've managed to receive:--> An award for outstanding performance within 1 year in an organisation (normally this award is given only after 2-3 years in the org.) working as an Informatica Powercenter Developer--> A chance to create IP utilities working on Informatica Developer tool (IDQ 9.X) which has also been praised by various heads in the org.--> Informatica Certified Specialist certification & official training through Informatica University which helped me become the \"go-to person\" in the organisation for Informatica related queries / help. At multiple occasions, people wi Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:12:27.028Z"),
    "question" : "What is career growth and salary hike for an Informatica developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603626a10c817f0398fa1edd"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-learn-application-development-or-web-development?-",
    "answer" : "As Richard Kenneth pointed out, web development is part of app development. But, allow me to take a different approach.  [image source : Aras | Enterprise PLM Software | Product Lifecycle Management ] Web App Development This is basically about creating web systems [read websites]. With most services moving to the web, it means you have a wider audience. Main examples are : Gmail for email, Office Online for Microsoft office services, even photo editing and video editing services can be found online. The main advantages of web systems over mobile and desktop apps are: Users don't need to install anythingUsers don't need to update anything. All updates are done on the system itself.Users using different devices and operating systems can use your system comfortably.Mobile and Desktop App Developm Continue Reading As Richard Kenneth pointed out, web development is part of app development. But, allow me to take a different approach.  [image source : Aras | Enterprise PLM Software | Product Lifecycle Management ] Web App Development This is basically about creating web systems [read websites]. With most services moving to the web, it means you have a wider audience. Main examples are : Gmail for email, Office Online for Microsoft office services, even photo editing and video editing services can be found online. The main advantages of web systems over mobile and desktop apps are: Users don't need to install anythingUsers don't need to update anything. All updates are done on the system itself.Users using different devices and operating systems can use your system comfortably.Mobile and Desktop App Developm Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:12:49.302Z"),
    "question" : "Should I learn application development or web development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603626b90c817f0398fa1f1d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-Python-help-in-career-development?-",
    "answer" : "Neha L Learning Python can help in career development in several ways. Python is a powerful, yet easy to learn programming language. Python itself provides plenty of job opportunities in IT sector, and various other sectors as well. Besides, Python is also the most preferred programming language by Data Scientists and Machine Learning professionals. So, after learning python, one can choose top go for python coding, or in Data Science or Machine Learning field. According to Indeed, the average salary of a Python Developer in the USA is $120,010. Top 3 states which pays highest salary for Python Developer includes: California,Washington DC andNew YorkMajor uses of Python programming language, which makes it popular and great includes: Back-end API’sWebsites developmentGUI network serversMedia toolsDesContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:13:13.728Z"),
    "question" : "How does Python help in career development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603626d00c817f0398fa1f24"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Has-anyone-used-Quora-for-career-opportunities-or-professional-connection-development?-",
    "answer" : "Agents will look under every rock for book/TV/movie ideas. So I wouldn’t be surprised if there have been some deals made on Quora with a quirky trivia writer here, personal essayist there, or those who seem to have legit entertainment/political gossip. But more likely, Quora is used at any stage in a person’s career to help keep their name circulating any way they can. They can use Quora as a backlink for their website and also a link to books and articles. Working writers, like Thomas Friedman, have Quora accounts. I can only guess that he has someone write his answers and it’s a way to keep promoting his books and name. If he didn’t have someone write his answers, it wouldn’t really be worth his time - though when you know your topic, you can churn these out quickly. Others can use Quora  Continue Reading Agents will look under every rock for book/TV/movie ideas. So I wouldn’t be surprised if there have been some deals made on Quora with a quirky trivia writer here, personal essayist there, or those who seem to have legit entertainment/political gossip. But more likely, Quora is used at any stage in a person’s career to help keep their name circulating any way they can. They can use Quora as a backlink for their website and also a link to books and articles. Working writers, like Thomas Friedman, have Quora accounts. I can only guess that he has someone write his answers and it’s a way to keep promoting his books and name. If he didn’t have someone write his answers, it wouldn’t really be worth his time - though when you know your topic, you can churn these out quickly. Others can use Quora  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:13:36.352Z"),
    "question" : "Has anyone used Quora for career opportunities or professional connection development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603626e30c817f0398fa1f2c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-best-digital-marketing-or-business-development?-",
    "answer" : "Digital marketing is about the ACT of creating strategies and implementing them through various testing cycles in different digital mediums to market your product/service to your audience. It's about how you deliver and spread the word about your product/service and it's content, with a goal-oriented objective in mind (getting an email from an user, making a sale, or branding, etc). There are multiple parts to digital marketing and requires a wide range of skills necessary to produce the whole funnel from A to Z. You need to be able to research and find competitive advantages to bring value in your marketing, and know how to implement these advantages into marketing strategies. Some skills necessary are: Website development (registering domains, setting up hosting, creating website, plugin  Continue Reading Digital marketing is about the ACT of creating strategies and implementing them through various testing cycles in different digital mediums to market your product/service to your audience. It's about how you deliver and spread the word about your product/service and it's content, with a goal-oriented objective in mind (getting an email from an user, making a sale, or branding, etc). There are multiple parts to digital marketing and requires a wide range of skills necessary to produce the whole funnel from A to Z. You need to be able to research and find competitive advantages to bring value in your marketing, and know how to implement these advantages into marketing strategies. Some skills necessary are: Website development (registering domains, setting up hosting, creating website, plugin  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:13:55.725Z"),
    "question" : "Which is best digital marketing or business development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603626f70c817f0398fa1f6a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-staying-an-individual-contributor-software-engineer-your-whole-life-a-good-career-choice?-Can-one-still-be-as-competitive-on-an-IC-track-as-he/she-would-be-on-a-managerial/executive-track?-Are-IC-developers-with-20+-years-experience-valued?-",
    "answer" : "If you're really good at engineering, you have a choice; if you are only kinda good, you should think about management. If you are truly good, 20+ years of experience is valued much higher than 5+ years. You'll definitely have to put in time to pick up new languages and frameworks, but your experience architecting systems and seeing companies through phases of success & failure will be incomparable to that of a spring chicken's. Some of the wisest engineers I know are incredibly senior, have intentionally stayed individual contributors, and stay out of all forms of management (and hence deal with the minimal amount of politics and thrash possible). It's a good life. You may not get the ego boost of a fancy title and sometimes managers will make more than you, but it's a good life. If you enj Continue Reading If you're really good at engineering, you have a choice; if you are only kinda good, you should think about management. If you are truly good, 20+ years of experience is valued much higher than 5+ years. You'll definitely have to put in time to pick up new languages and frameworks, but your experience architecting systems and seeing companies through phases of success & failure will be incomparable to that of a spring chicken's. Some of the wisest engineers I know are incredibly senior, have intentionally stayed individual contributors, and stay out of all forms of management (and hence deal with the minimal amount of politics and thrash possible). It's a good life. You may not get the ego boost of a fancy title and sometimes managers will make more than you, but it's a good life. If you enj Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:14:15.753Z"),
    "question" : "Is staying an individual contributor software engineer your whole life a good career choice? Can one still be as competitive on an IC track as he/she would be on a managerial/executive track? Are IC developers with 20+ years experience valued? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603627230c817f0398fa1f76"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-develop-my-career-in-software?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How can I develop my career in software?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:14:59.407Z"),
    "question" : "How can I develop my career in software? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362be80c817f0398fa2539"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What’s-the-typical-career-path-for-a-business-development-associate?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What’s the typical career path for a business development associate?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:35:20.735Z"),
    "question" : "What’s the typical career path for a business development associate? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362c110c817f0398fa254b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-of-the-good-books-on-career-counseling?-",
    "answer" : "You did not specify a specific career, SO I will answer this generally. I recommend you read “Living with a Seal” by Jesse Itzler. In this book,Jesse Itzler tells the story of doing a 100-mile run as part of a six person relay team. There was a 260-pound US Navy Seal who was also running in this race but he was running it entirely by himself. By the end of the race he had broken all the small bones in both of his feet and had kidney damage but he finished the race. After the race Jesse asked him to live with him for a while to teach him this level of endurance. The Seal agreed and one of the most important lessons he taught was this:“When your mind is telling you you’re done, you’re really only 40 percent done.” If you want a successful Career, You will not achieve it halfheartedly. It would Continue Reading You did not specify a specific career, SO I will answer this generally. I recommend you read “Living with a Seal” by Jesse Itzler. In this book,Jesse Itzler tells the story of doing a 100-mile run as part of a six person relay team. There was a 260-pound US Navy Seal who was also running in this race but he was running it entirely by himself. By the end of the race he had broken all the small bones in both of his feet and had kidney damage but he finished the race. After the race Jesse asked him to live with him for a while to teach him this level of endurance. The Seal agreed and one of the most important lessons he taught was this:“When your mind is telling you you’re done, you’re really only 40 percent done.” If you want a successful Career, You will not achieve it halfheartedly. It would Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:36:01.452Z"),
    "question" : "What are some of the good books on career counseling? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362c360c817f0398fa258b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-front-end-web-development-good-enough-to-be-pursued-as-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is front-end web development good enough to be pursued as a career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:36:38.821Z"),
    "question" : "Is front-end web development good enough to be pursued as a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362c4a0c817f0398fa2593"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-choose-software-development-or-Cyber-Security-as-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Ramandeep Sethi 5",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:36:58.668Z"),
    "question" : "Should I choose software development or Cyber Security as a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362c710c817f0398fa25d5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-build-an-unstressful-software-developer-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I build an unstressful software developer career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:37:37.064Z"),
    "question" : "How do I build an unstressful software developer career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362c970c817f0398fa2617"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-about-the-career-as-a-SQL-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How about the career as a SQL developer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:38:15.245Z"),
    "question" : "How about the career as a SQL developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362cee0c817f0398fa2665"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-better-to-pursue-Developer-career-than-the-career-as-a-tester?-",
    "answer" : "A2A! Hello! The below thoughts/suggestions are purely based on my perspectives. Be clear on your career goals and aspirations. After a period of time, say 6–7 years there is a fair possibility to get into people management/leading teams. So what is that you are looking for? Do you want to continue into technical side for a very long time in your career span? As some one quoted below - Testing is a zero brain activity. No it is not. If someone can assess your work, do you think they are brainless? Your capability and potential is always questioned by a tester. Coming to the question - Prioritize your long term aspirations. Do you like programming? Do you have that zeal and enthusiasm in you? OR are you willing to take it up as a challenge? Go ahead! You have a long way in your career to leave y Continue Reading A2A! Hello! The below thoughts/suggestions are purely based on my perspectives. Be clear on your career goals and aspirations. After a period of time, say 6–7 years there is a fair possibility to get into people management/leading teams. So what is that you are looking for? Do you want to continue into technical side for a very long time in your career span? As some one quoted below - Testing is a zero brain activity. No it is not. If someone can assess your work, do you think they are brainless? Your capability and potential is always questioned by a tester. Coming to the question - Prioritize your long term aspirations. Do you like programming? Do you have that zeal and enthusiasm in you? OR are you willing to take it up as a challenge? Go ahead! You have a long way in your career to leave y Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:39:42.159Z"),
    "question" : "Is it better to pursue Developer career than the career as a tester? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362d260c817f0398fa26b1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-H1B-limit-your-career-development-in-USA?-",
    "answer" : "Here is my take from my friend’s perspective. He came to the USA after graduating from IIT Kharagpur. Even I don’t know why he came to the USA after graduating from IIT. Probably he was following the trend. He joined a major bank after securing OPT, after completing MS from the USA. Got good grades there too. In that major bank, he was given the work which was not at par his talent and abilities. Then he thought, H1B is important. Let’s ruin a couple of years of the career and then we will start again after H1B. He has worked with the abusive manager and survived a hostile work environment in that stupid major bank throughout his tenure. But they filed his H1B. probably because no one else was joining that team. He did not get H1B in the first attempt. H1B lottery does not care about good grade Continue Reading Here is my take from my friend’s perspective. He came to the USA after graduating from IIT Kharagpur. Even I don’t know why he came to the USA after graduating from IIT. Probably he was following the trend. He joined a major bank after securing OPT, after completing MS from the USA. Got good grades there too. In that major bank, he was given the work which was not at par his talent and abilities. Then he thought, H1B is important. Let’s ruin a couple of years of the career and then we will start again after H1B. He has worked with the abusive manager and survived a hostile work environment in that stupid major bank throughout his tenure. But they filed his H1B. probably because no one else was joining that team. He did not get H1B in the first attempt. H1B lottery does not care about good grade Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:40:38.983Z"),
    "question" : "How does H1B limit your career development in USA? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362d4d0c817f0398fa26f4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-languages-do-you-recommend-new-coders-start-with?-I-was-told-to-start-with-Python,-but-I-was-thinking-of-going-into-HTML-and-CSS,-then-Javascript-for-web-development.-What-is-the-best-plan-for-a-career-path-in-this-field?-",
    "answer" : "Follow what your heart says, if you want to learn HTML , CSS and JavaScript then learn it without any single thought, and to be frank I honestly believe its a fantastic choice. Arguably JavaScript has become the most important language today. Here is a short list why you should try JavaScript(I answered it earlier for a question related to Javascript) JavaScript is the only programming language understood by browser, you don’t have choiceFront-end development needs JavaScript. Angular, React and Vue are are some of popular choices you have.Back-end development - You are not happy with just front-end ? you want more knowledge. Great! I have a good news for you, now you don’t have to learn an extra language like Java, PHP, Python or Ruby for that. With the power of Node.js you can do back-endContinue Reading Follow what your heart says, if you want to learn HTML , CSS and JavaScript then learn it without any single thought, and to be frank I honestly believe its a fantastic choice. Arguably JavaScript has become the most important language today. Here is a short list why you should try JavaScript(I answered it earlier for a question related to Javascript) JavaScript is the only programming language understood by browser, you don’t have choiceFront-end development needs JavaScript. Angular, React and Vue are are some of popular choices you have.Back-end development - You are not happy with just front-end ? you want more knowledge. Great! I have a good news for you, now you don’t have to learn an extra language like Java, PHP, Python or Ruby for that. With the power of Node.js you can do back-endContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:41:17.858Z"),
    "question" : "What languages do you recommend new coders start with? I was told to start with Python, but I was thinking of going into HTML and CSS, then Javascript for web development. What is the best plan for a career path in this field? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362d720c817f0398fa26ff"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-hard-is-it-to-work-as-a-software-developer?-",
    "answer" : "“Is it hard to become a software developer?” Yes. Comp Sci and Soft Eng are usually considered among the hardest majors on campus. There are a lot of nit-picking details to master, there is a lot of homework. You are well-advised to participate in big group projects. You are well advised to make up a portfolio of work that you can showcase to potential employers. You are well advised to do an internship or two. No summer breaks sightseeing in Europe for you. One of the biggest obstacles for some students is that computers can’t be socially engineered. You can’t beg for mercy, claim victim group status, or demand an A for effort. You have to write code that works, and computers are merciless at finding flaws in your code. But getting your degree is the easy part! Once you get your degree, you di Continue Reading “Is it hard to become a software developer?” Yes. Comp Sci and Soft Eng are usually considered among the hardest majors on campus. There are a lot of nit-picking details to master, there is a lot of homework. You are well-advised to participate in big group projects. You are well advised to make up a portfolio of work that you can showcase to potential employers. You are well advised to do an internship or two. No summer breaks sightseeing in Europe for you. One of the biggest obstacles for some students is that computers can’t be socially engineered. You can’t beg for mercy, claim victim group status, or demand an A for effort. You have to write code that works, and computers are merciless at finding flaws in your code. But getting your degree is the easy part! Once you get your degree, you di Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:41:54.312Z"),
    "question" : "How hard is it to work as a software developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362dae0c817f0398fa2747"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-dark-sides-of-a-career-in-web-development?-",
    "answer" : "Anashku I guess I can answer this but not at full potential as I haven't experienced much of it yet as I just started my career. I pursued web development as a passion in tech or IT field. The dark sides are - a fresher with web development knowledge getting hired chances are too less , I know there are thousands of openings for web development but all of them require min 2+ years experience which I definitely don't how one should get the experience unless he or she gets a chance to get experience. I personally suffered this.Next I had interned to a company , they needed front end developers for the website and after the product or project was complete they longer needed the web development team , they dissolved it and the internship ended. Few companies gets contracts without breaks but 50% of co Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:42:54.612Z"),
    "question" : "What are the dark sides of a career in web development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362de50c817f0398fa278e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-web-development-still-a-viable-career-choice-in-2019?-",
    "answer" : "Aftab Alam  Yes, Web development is still a viable career option in 2019 and it is in continuous boom at the moment. To give best to client and the to serve best to consumer, day by day the requirement of good and professional developers are increasing. If you are planning to be a developer than you can think about it, but don’t be a ordinary developer, try to become a professional/expert developer.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:43:49.966Z"),
    "question" : "Is web development still a viable career choice in 2019? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362e000c817f0398fa27ce"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-decision-of-your-software-development-career?-",
    "answer" : "Ironically, for me it was to stop coding and commit myself to the business areas of the technology industry. Business was my true passion, and technology was where my obsession or interest was in, not software development. You see I was trained in Computer Science and graduated at the top of my class with my soon to be business partner in a few years time (not knowing yet back then). I always had the impression that you needed to know how to code well in order to build a technology business, and although I did well in my Computer Science projects and studies, I simply dreaded it every time I had to look at binary codes, memory arrays, sorting algorithms, memory management and the goddamn network topology design. So there I was going through the whole course and when I started working, I reali Continue Reading Ironically, for me it was to stop coding and commit myself to the business areas of the technology industry. Business was my true passion, and technology was where my obsession or interest was in, not software development. You see I was trained in Computer Science and graduated at the top of my class with my soon to be business partner in a few years time (not knowing yet back then). I always had the impression that you needed to know how to code well in order to build a technology business, and although I did well in my Computer Science projects and studies, I simply dreaded it every time I had to look at binary codes, memory arrays, sorting algorithms, memory management and the goddamn network topology design. So there I was going through the whole course and when I started working, I reali Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:44:16.882Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best decision of your software development career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362e140c817f0398fa27d4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-there-any-career-for-game-development-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is there any career for game development in India?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:44:36.448Z"),
    "question" : "Is there any career for game development in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362e270c817f0398fa27db"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-web-development-a-good-career-in-2021?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is web development a good career in 2021?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:44:55.134Z"),
    "question" : "Is web development a good career in 2021? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362e4d0c817f0398fa2820"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-job-satisfaction-in-career-development?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is job satisfaction in career development?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:45:33.772Z"),
    "question" : "What is job satisfaction in career development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362e620c817f0398fa2829"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-make-a-good-career-in-the-data-analytics-industry?-What-are-the-skills-I-need-to-develop-if-I-have-to-start-from-scratch?-",
    "answer" : "Data analytics has gained humongous popularity over the past few years and has become a hot topic in the market since data is at the core of the technology. Demand for data analysts with the right skill set and knowledge will keep increasing with billions of data getting generated every day. There is an umpteenth number of opportunities that span across multiple industries for you to explore since making a career in analytics is promising for people of all backgrounds. Let's find out why one should pursue a Career in Data Analytics? High salary at entry-level and excellent perks - Data analysts are paid very well in the industry even at entry-level since there are limited data analysts in the market. Data analysis is one of the most sought after jobs in the market and there is no denying tha Continue Reading Data analytics has gained humongous popularity over the past few years and has become a hot topic in the market since data is at the core of the technology. Demand for data analysts with the right skill set and knowledge will keep increasing with billions of data getting generated every day. There is an umpteenth number of opportunities that span across multiple industries for you to explore since making a career in analytics is promising for people of all backgrounds. Let's find out why one should pursue a Career in Data Analytics? High salary at entry-level and excellent perks - Data analysts are paid very well in the industry even at entry-level since there are limited data analysts in the market. Data analysis is one of the most sought after jobs in the market and there is no denying tha Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:45:54.560Z"),
    "question" : "How can I make a good career in the data analytics industry? What are the skills I need to develop if I have to start from scratch? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362e750c817f0398fa2866"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-a-career-in-Android-development-in-2016?-",
    "answer" : "Ahaa! When it comes to predict about anything related to technology it’s bit tough. Current era is all about the technology. Android OS ruling the marketing since long. Even we have seen there are lots of websites who are leading the web since long stop their services from the web and promote a lot their mobile application. We can say that, Not only Android but iOS Windows and other mobile OS platforms have a bright future as people are getting more and more engage with smartphone. A perfect example for the same you can read it below with statistics:- Ahaa! When it comes to predict about anything relevant to technological innovation it’s bit challenging. Present era is all about the technological innovation. Android OS ruling the market since long. Even we have seen there are plenty of sites wh Continue Reading Ahaa! When it comes to predict about anything related to technology it’s bit tough. Current era is all about the technology. Android OS ruling the marketing since long. Even we have seen there are lots of websites who are leading the web since long stop their services from the web and promote a lot their mobile application. We can say that, Not only Android but iOS Windows and other mobile OS platforms have a bright future as people are getting more and more engage with smartphone. A perfect example for the same you can read it below with statistics:- Ahaa! When it comes to predict about anything relevant to technological innovation it’s bit challenging. Present era is all about the technological innovation. Android OS ruling the market since long. Even we have seen there are plenty of sites wh Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:46:13.421Z"),
    "question" : "How good is a career in Android development in 2016? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362e8a0c817f0398fa286c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-languages-should-I-focus-on-when-starting-a-career-as-a-software-developer?-",
    "answer" : "The answer below assumes that the person asking the question is not acquainted with software development yet. If you already know basic programming, please check out the other advice being offered. If you don’t know anything about programming, read on. Beginners assume that learning to become a software developer is about a specific language or technology. But actually, the language you use is just a tool. Think of the difference between, say, carpentry and knowing how to swing a hammer. Software works the same way. There are certain foundational processes, concepts, techniques, and ways of thinking that are necessary to develop. You can develop those skills in a variety of languages. For a beginner, I would say start by learning a general-purpose “imperative” programming language that will  Continue Reading The answer below assumes that the person asking the question is not acquainted with software development yet. If you already know basic programming, please check out the other advice being offered. If you don’t know anything about programming, read on. Beginners assume that learning to become a software developer is about a specific language or technology. But actually, the language you use is just a tool. Think of the difference between, say, carpentry and knowing how to swing a hammer. Software works the same way. There are certain foundational processes, concepts, techniques, and ways of thinking that are necessary to develop. You can develop those skills in a variety of languages. For a beginner, I would say start by learning a general-purpose “imperative” programming language that will  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:46:34.217Z"),
    "question" : "What languages should I focus on when starting a career as a software developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362e9c0c817f0398fa2874"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-of-web-development-career-and-the-web-in-general?-",
    "answer" : "Anthony Wijaya, if I'm bored out of my mind, I write hereAnswered 4 years agoWhat is the future of web development career and the web in general? Anthony Wijaya Normal websites/ personal websites are definitely not going anywhere. At least I know I won't.  So yes, web development will still be in demand for at least another one or two decades. Facebook or twitter or google will never change this fact. (unless they have some secret plan that will prove me otherwise) As for the future, well, let's first talk about the near future (1-3 years), because at the pace the web is growing right now, I'm not sure anyone can predict where we're going. In this time scale, I expect that things are going to pick up really quick, what's with the new frameworks that seemed to pop up every week or so. This means that you will need to learn a lot of things and you will need to learn it fast. I'm not sure the right word is 'harder' but I think web development does have  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:46:52.835Z"),
    "question" : "What is the future of web development career and the web in general? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362eae0c817f0398fa28b2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-java-developer-a-good-career-growth?-",
    "answer" : "Even after over 22 years of presence, Java is available all over. It's in logical supercomputers, PCs, cell phones, gaming supports, and so on With IT abilities in incredible interest everywhere in the world, choosing to turn into a Java designer can open energizing occasions to propel your profession in both people in general and private area. It is a programming language which is continually filling in notoriety and you can be guaranteed that Java is staying put for an exceptionally lengthy timespan. Here's all you require to think about the profession development of filling in as a Java Developer. Profession Path Of Java Developers Contingent upon your insight and experience, you will typically continue in your expert profession along the accompanying way Junior Programmer When you land your Continue Reading Even after over 22 years of presence, Java is available all over. It's in logical supercomputers, PCs, cell phones, gaming supports, and so on With IT abilities in incredible interest everywhere in the world, choosing to turn into a Java designer can open energizing occasions to propel your profession in both people in general and private area. It is a programming language which is continually filling in notoriety and you can be guaranteed that Java is staying put for an exceptionally lengthy timespan. Here's all you require to think about the profession development of filling in as a Java Developer. Profession Path Of Java Developers Contingent upon your insight and experience, you will typically continue in your expert profession along the accompanying way Junior Programmer When you land your Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:47:10.736Z"),
    "question" : "Is a java developer a good career growth? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362ee30c817f0398fa28c2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-iOS-app-development-a-good-career-in-2016?-",
    "answer" : "Dharmendra Singh I would say YES!. Because according to Edureka, Demand for iOS Skills: The world has an insatiable appetite for new and better apps. Developers have numerous chances to exhibit their skill by developing interesting and innovative apps that run on iOS. With the growing popularity of iPhones, iPads and iPods and the appetite for new apps, we can expect a steady demand for iOS developers who can work some magic when it comes to developing apps.  The graph above from Indeed, a popular job portal illustrates the demand for this skill. If that is not convincing, here are some predictions of the ios market and the job demand by Joe Conway, Founder of Stable / Kernel, and author of ‘iOS Programming: The Big Nerd Ranch Guide’. According to Joe, the demand for iOS Developers will remain high through 2015 Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:48:03.510Z"),
    "question" : "Is iOS app development a good career in 2016? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362f0c0c817f0398fa2904"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-five-stages-of-career-development?-",
    "answer" : "Stage # 1. Exploration: The exploratory stage is the period of transition from college to work, that is, the period immediately prior to employment. It is usually the period of one’s early 20 s and ends by mid-20 s. It is a stage of self-exploration and making preliminary choices. Stage # 2. Establishment: This career stage begins when one starts seeking for work. It includes getting one’s first job. Hence, during this stage, one is likely to commit mistakes; one has also the opportunities to learn from such mistakes and may also assume greater responsibilities. He/ she accepts job challenges and develops competence in a speculating area. He/she develops creativity and rotates into a new area after three-five years. Stage # 3. Mid-Career: During this stage, the performance may increase or decre Continue Reading Stage # 1. Exploration: The exploratory stage is the period of transition from college to work, that is, the period immediately prior to employment. It is usually the period of one’s early 20 s and ends by mid-20 s. It is a stage of self-exploration and making preliminary choices. Stage # 2. Establishment: This career stage begins when one starts seeking for work. It includes getting one’s first job. Hence, during this stage, one is likely to commit mistakes; one has also the opportunities to learn from such mistakes and may also assume greater responsibilities. He/ she accepts job challenges and develops competence in a speculating area. He/she develops creativity and rotates into a new area after three-five years. Stage # 3. Mid-Career: During this stage, the performance may increase or decre Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:48:44.841Z"),
    "question" : "What are the five stages of career development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362f370c817f0398fa2947"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-biggest-mistakes-that-you-have-made-in-your-software-development-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the biggest mistakes that you have made in your software development career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:49:27.172Z"),
    "question" : "What are the biggest mistakes that you have made in your software development career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362f700c817f0398fa298e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-job-position-is-better-software-testing-or-software-development?-",
    "answer" : "Rakesh Depends on your skill,experience,attitude and most important your interest.  The Indian IT industry is mostly services based industry which relies mostly on two types of jobs : software development and software testing (QA). There are other streams too, but those are out of the scope of this discussion. We'll only focus on testing vs. development. Typically most big IT industries will take up projects from overseas clients and have engineers work on them. This leads to two career paths - Software Testing & Software Development. Overall - the software development teams are responsible for 'coding' and software testing teams are responsible for making sure that everything adheres to the specifications of the software being developed. Career Growth: Software testing and development engineers have Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:50:24.467Z"),
    "question" : "Which job position is better software testing or software development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362f920c817f0398fa299d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-web-development-a-stressful-career?-",
    "answer" : "Mike Danna Working in the web development space can be very rewarding, though, can also be very stressful — let's not forget, throw you into the realm of self-isolation. Trust me. Assuming you are passionate about what you are doing, there is nothing better than listening to some killer music and getting lost in your development production. Is Web Development A Stressful Career? Yes and no. It is vital to maintain confidence in your specific field and your ability to adapt and produce. If working under a company, you will need to meet the demands of ongoing, consistent work, which can sometimes feel like your performance is constantly under a microscope. If working independently as a freelancer, you will need to craft your personality traits to sustain control and objectivity between your relationship with Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:50:58.496Z"),
    "question" : "Is web development a stressful career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362fa60c817f0398fa29db"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-find-easy-web-development-freelance-jobs-to-start-out-my-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How can I find easy web development freelance jobs to start out my career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:51:18.851Z"),
    "question" : "How can I find easy web development freelance jobs to start out my career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362fbc0c817f0398fa29e1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-wordpress-developer-a-good-career?-",
    "answer" : "re: What is your workflow as a WordPress developer? (I don’t consider myself a ‘WordPress’ or any type of specific ‘developer’) I don’t always use WordPress… but when I do… MAMP Pro for the local server (mac) (text editor doesn’t matter but I still use Sublime)  SpinupWP for hosting dashboard + Digital Ocean droplets.  Tower for git. (only keep the theme and the plugins in here) (requires a little finesse at first to ensure you only keep these in spinup - and after that, it just works perfectly)  Custom Post Type UI for quick setup. (sometimes I just write them out)   ACF for custom fields. (couldn’t live without this one)  Build all the fields and content strategy with the client early on - and get the site live and ready for them to add the content - before even writing a bit of code. (maybe you’ll co Continue Reading re: What is your workflow as a WordPress developer? (I don’t consider myself a ‘WordPress’ or any type of specific ‘developer’) I don’t always use WordPress… but when I do… MAMP Pro for the local server (mac) (text editor doesn’t matter but I still use Sublime)  SpinupWP for hosting dashboard + Digital Ocean droplets.  Tower for git. (only keep the theme and the plugins in here) (requires a little finesse at first to ensure you only keep these in spinup - and after that, it just works perfectly)  Custom Post Type UI for quick setup. (sometimes I just write them out)   ACF for custom fields. (couldn’t live without this one)  Build all the fields and content strategy with the client early on - and get the site live and ready for them to add the content - before even writing a bit of code. (maybe you’ll co Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:51:40.088Z"),
    "question" : "Is wordpress developer a good career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362fd00c817f0398fa29eb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Will-Web-Development-still-be-a-viable-career-in-30-Years?-",
    "answer" : "A2A The question is good but it should be will have a same way of developing websites and same technology? of course NO but Internet is way of connecting the world through web and luckily we are connected through it and it will keep becoming bigger I can say that the way we develop the website might not the same but the demand of web applications will not go down. We will still need web developers but they have to be updated with the required technology. few years ago there was no concept of mobile friendly web apps but now it is one of the most in demand skill to have as web developer. web is the way we share information, data and so on and all because of we have great web engineers. Let me tell you one thing web development is not limited to developing nice blogs, websites if you explore it Continue Reading A2A The question is good but it should be will have a same way of developing websites and same technology? of course NO but Internet is way of connecting the world through web and luckily we are connected through it and it will keep becoming bigger I can say that the way we develop the website might not the same but the demand of web applications will not go down. We will still need web developers but they have to be updated with the required technology. few years ago there was no concept of mobile friendly web apps but now it is one of the most in demand skill to have as web developer. web is the way we share information, data and so on and all because of we have great web engineers. Let me tell you one thing web development is not limited to developing nice blogs, websites if you explore it Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:52:00.294Z"),
    "question" : "Will Web Development still be a viable career in 30 Years? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60362fe40c817f0398fa2a28"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-will-a-career-in-cloud-computing-be-vs-a-Java-developer-career?-",
    "answer" : "Cloud computing is growing at the rate of almost 15–20% YoY.  Even though the adoption to cloud computing has picked up over last 5 years, still a lot of migration is yet to happen. Even though they are into multiple businesses, but cloud computing platforms appeared to be game changer for companies like AMAZON and Microsoft. Cloud computing is today becoming a sort of de-facto go to platform. Off course Java developer has evergreen requirements and needs, but that is likely to get saturated over a period of time. My recommendation would be to go for Cloud computing rather than plane vanilla Java developer. Off course you would need to learn Java in any case for some areas of cloud computing Continue Reading Cloud computing is growing at the rate of almost 15–20% YoY.  Even though the adoption to cloud computing has picked up over last 5 years, still a lot of migration is yet to happen. Even though they are into multiple businesses, but cloud computing platforms appeared to be game changer for companies like AMAZON and Microsoft. Cloud computing is today becoming a sort of de-facto go to platform. Off course Java developer has evergreen requirements and needs, but that is likely to get saturated over a period of time. My recommendation would be to go for Cloud computing rather than plane vanilla Java developer. Off course you would need to learn Java in any case for some areas of cloud computing Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:52:20.982Z"),
    "question" : "How will a career in cloud computing be vs a Java developer career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036300a0c817f0398fa2a33"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-computer-science-help-me-in-my-career-development?-",
    "answer" : "If you are a professional in computer science, quite a lot. Since you can apply most but all the concepts learned in the development of your professional activity. For example, if you are a programmer, computer science has a good programming base, that is, all applications and computer programs are developed through this activity. If you are a network or database administrator, in computer science you teach a good part of these concepts. On the other hand, most of the activities we do today are related in some way to computer science. For example, surf the Internet, use a chat application, use social networks, online shopping, mobile phones, etc. All these activities involve computer science, so it is very useful to handle at least the basic concepts. Finally, to take a course or training in Continue Reading If you are a professional in computer science, quite a lot. Since you can apply most but all the concepts learned in the development of your professional activity. For example, if you are a programmer, computer science has a good programming base, that is, all applications and computer programs are developed through this activity. If you are a network or database administrator, in computer science you teach a good part of these concepts. On the other hand, most of the activities we do today are related in some way to computer science. For example, surf the Internet, use a chat application, use social networks, online shopping, mobile phones, etc. All these activities involve computer science, so it is very useful to handle at least the basic concepts. Finally, to take a course or training in Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:52:58.334Z"),
    "question" : "How does computer science help me in my career development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603630330c817f0398fa2a75"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-business-development-executive-a-good-career-choice?-",
    "answer" : "Business Development can be a great choice if you are ready to take up challenging task. When you are interested to meet people, understand their need and fulfill their goals, then you get the reward, you will feel great. You will get a lot of job satisfaction. It is good to be a business developer when you have the passion of building relationship with others. An individual can build a good career in business development and it depends on the company also. If the company is good, then the person will be motivated to work hard. There must be incentive along with the salary. You can go through youtube and google and learn new techniques of business development. In this way, you can advertise and take up projects in India and abroad. You can help startup establish their business. If you get p Continue Reading Business Development can be a great choice if you are ready to take up challenging task. When you are interested to meet people, understand their need and fulfill their goals, then you get the reward, you will feel great. You will get a lot of job satisfaction. It is good to be a business developer when you have the passion of building relationship with others. An individual can build a good career in business development and it depends on the company also. If the company is good, then the person will be motivated to work hard. There must be incentive along with the salary. You can go through youtube and google and learn new techniques of business development. In this way, you can advertise and take up projects in India and abroad. You can help startup establish their business. If you get p Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:53:39.428Z"),
    "question" : "Is a business development executive a good career choice? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036305c0c817f0398fa2ab9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Android-development-a-good-career-for-starting-as-a-fresher?-",
    "answer" : "Not at all. See first of all let’s talk about the differences between an application and an website. Website is kind of one time interaction thing. You visit the website, do your work and go back. But in context of application the application remains in your phone, it gives you assistance, it works for you constantly, it makes your life easier, it helps you in so many ways by collecting different kind of data. So basic thing in market which is going wrong is people place application and website on same scale. They do not find the actual meaning of application when their business actually needs application. Mobile is an personal thing, so as applications. Users give space to only applications which really help them in real life. Users barely stores flipkart or amazon on their phone for long Continue Reading Not at all. See first of all let’s talk about the differences between an application and an website. Website is kind of one time interaction thing. You visit the website, do your work and go back. But in context of application the application remains in your phone, it gives you assistance, it works for you constantly, it makes your life easier, it helps you in so many ways by collecting different kind of data. So basic thing in market which is going wrong is people place application and website on same scale. They do not find the actual meaning of application when their business actually needs application. Mobile is an personal thing, so as applications. Users give space to only applications which really help them in real life. Users barely stores flipkart or amazon on their phone for long Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:54:20.325Z"),
    "question" : "Is Android development a good career for starting as a fresher? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603630820c817f0398fa2ac5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-LinkedIn-help-you-in-your-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How does LinkedIn help you in your career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:54:58.749Z"),
    "question" : "How does LinkedIn help you in your career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603630950c817f0398fa2b03"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-has-better-career-opportunities-frontend-development-or-Android-development?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which has better career opportunities frontend development or Android development?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:55:17.700Z"),
    "question" : "Which has better career opportunities frontend development or Android development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603630bc0c817f0398fa2b13"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-opportunities-for-a-blockchain-developer-today?-",
    "answer" : "Rakesh Sharma Blockchain development is a new field for software engineers and as it always happen when there is a latest tech there are very few developers, once the tech is old and established then there are many people persuing it, but on the contarary the less people doing it makes it more lucrative to those doing it. Although this is not at all a different language or tech, it's just an upgraded version of old c encryption algorithms and an application of old tech in some useful manner. It's good time to get into the business right now, make some buck and later you can always change to some another tech. After all engineers are ment to work on technologies not stick to them. Thanks An upvote is appreciated. Aman Swali",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:55:56.587Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career opportunities for a blockchain developer today? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603630e10c817f0398fa2b53"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-did-you-choose-your-career-in-software-development?-",
    "answer" : "Abhilash Gopalakrishnan My bachelors was in Mechanical Engineering. While I loved the machines and mechanics, I should admit neither did I focus on the math behind it nor really analyze how it works. Should say was lazy. But towards the end of course we had Pascal and C in syllabus. Somehow I liked it and loved time in Computer Lab. This was interesting. I could create lot of new things in a few hours in lab. (Suggested by a friend Manoj) I started spending time in lab with my friends (my buddies even now) who were doing some interesting programs. This changed my life. I had done a small management information system as part of our mech project. When I graduated I realized what I really learnt or rather my strength was in creating programs. While I joined my first job at a Glass Factory as apprentice and got chanc Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:56:33.421Z"),
    "question" : "Why did you choose your career in software development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603630f20c817f0398fa2b5b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-different-is-the-career-path-between-mobile-app-developer-and-web-developer?-",
    "answer" : "They are completely different. Mobile apps are written in a platform independent language like Java, and down loaded to be executed on the client machine.Web developers instead use JavaScript, html, css, PHP and other tools to tell the browser what a page should look like and do. You don't  run your own code but instead your code puts together pages for the client brower to interpret.The closest thing to real code is event handler script snippets. Jereme Causing",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:56:50.872Z"),
    "question" : "How different is the career path between mobile app developer and web developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603631050c817f0398fa2b65"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-did-getting-a-PhD-help-you-become-the-person-that-you-are?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How did getting a PhD help you become the person that you are?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:57:09.473Z"),
    "question" : "How did getting a PhD help you become the person that you are? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603631170c817f0398fa2b9f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-the-career-as-a-RPA-developer?-",
    "answer" : "According to McKinsey Research, Knowledge in work automation could have economic impact of $5-7 trillion by the year 2025. It will touch more than 230 million knowledge workers, nine percent of the global workforce In a typical RPA project, there are majorly 3 types of responsibilities involved: Process DesignerAutomation ArchitectProduction ManagerProcess Designer: The Process Designer is responsible for understanding the current process.He/she makes sure that the people working on the RPA project are in sync.He/She also works monitoring the the changes happen after implementing the feedback during development or testing phase while keeping the project specifications intactAutomation Architect: Automation Architect builds the RPA project using the RPA tooling.He/she is the member of core automation team and may or maynot have the developer level expertise depending upon the RPA tool the organisation is using.The automation architect still have some experience in the programming and solving real world problem.Production Manager: After the RPA project is tested and goes into the production, the project’s responsibility comes on the Production Manager. The following are some of the responsibilities of a Production Manager: Monitoring if the process is triggered as per the scheduleHandling the exceptions occurred in the processReporting bugs to the Automation Architect and making sure that they are resolved/fixedMonitoring and reviewing the process analytics and conveying the process improvement information to the Process DesignerIf you are thinking of a career in Robotic Process Automation(RPA), you should definitely start gaining skills and go for it as a career in this field is considered to be very effective in one’s career development.As many organisations are implementing the Process Automation, the future scope of this technology very high and it will generate a major share of employment opportunities in the coming years.The pay scale of the people who are experts in RPA is relatively much higher in comparison with the other fields.To avail these high ranging career opportunities provided by the field of RPA, one should leverage their skills in the RPA technology.For beginners, it is best to start learning about the Robotic Process Automation by taking a course in RPA from Edureka who are currently delivering the best training in RPA using UiPath.More of my useful answers on RPA: How is the market for robotics process automation? Saurav's answer to How is the market for robotics process automation?Why learn RPA using UiPath tool? You can find out here: Saurav's answer to Which is the best RPA tool?What does it take to be an RPA developer? (Saurav's answer to What does it take to be an RPA developer? What sort of coding is required if any?)How you should start learning RPA? Find here: Saurav's answer to How should I start learning RPA?If you have found my answer relevant, kindly Upvote my answer. If any more questions drop a Comment.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:57:27.573Z"),
    "question" : "How is the career as a RPA developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036313c0c817f0398fa2bab"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-of-a-full-stack-web-developer?-",
    "answer" : "MERN Stack: MERN Stack is one of the latest and most popular open source web development tools based on different JavaScript technologies. MERN is an acronym given to the combination of JavaScript technologies MongoDB (M), Express JS (E), React JS, (R) and Node JS (N) as it has the ability to develop dynamic websites and web applications capable of performing every function that these individual components perform. Thus, it allows the full stack development using only a single language, JavaScript. MERN Stack training course highlights: · The Understanding synergy of Node JS, React JS, Express JS, and MongoDB · Learning API development using MongoDB, Express JS and React JS · Learning to develop MERN applications using various JavaScript technologies · Understanding server application developmen Continue Reading MERN Stack: MERN Stack is one of the latest and most popular open source web development tools based on different JavaScript technologies. MERN is an acronym given to the combination of JavaScript technologies MongoDB (M), Express JS (E), React JS, (R) and Node JS (N) as it has the ability to develop dynamic websites and web applications capable of performing every function that these individual components perform. Thus, it allows the full stack development using only a single language, JavaScript. MERN Stack training course highlights: · The Understanding synergy of Node JS, React JS, Express JS, and MongoDB · Learning API development using MongoDB, Express JS and React JS · Learning to develop MERN applications using various JavaScript technologies · Understanding server application developmen Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:58:04.197Z"),
    "question" : "What is the future of a full-stack web developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036314d0c817f0398fa2be7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-of-a-PHP-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Learning a new programming language is not hard and you’ll have a greater vision about programming once you learnt it. No one is able to tell you the future of the PHP (or any programming language) accurately. One big reason for this is the marketing of new programming languages by tech companies. They can quickly (3–5 years) make some language very very popular. The other reason is the change in the tech industry at a higher scope. AI for example. Or blockchain algorithms. They can easily make some programming language obsolete in a short time. The advantages and disadvantages of programming languages change over time. The developer (or company) should write code in a language that fits best to the needs, not in a single language he/she knows. One project may be written in 2 or 3 languages. Continue Reading Learning a new programming language is not hard and you’ll have a greater vision about programming once you learnt it. No one is able to tell you the future of the PHP (or any programming language) accurately. One big reason for this is the marketing of new programming languages by tech companies. They can quickly (3–5 years) make some language very very popular. The other reason is the change in the tech industry at a higher scope. AI for example. Or blockchain algorithms. They can easily make some programming language obsolete in a short time. The advantages and disadvantages of programming languages change over time. The developer (or company) should write code in a language that fits best to the needs, not in a single language he/she knows. One project may be written in 2 or 3 languages. Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:58:21.441Z"),
    "question" : "What is the future of a PHP developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603631620c817f0398fa2bed"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-improvement-areas-in-career-growth?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the improvement areas in career growth?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:58:42.438Z"),
    "question" : "What are the improvement areas in career growth? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603631740c817f0398fa2bf7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-typical-career-progression-at-Deloitte?-",
    "answer" : "Roy Raymondo  Arnab Kumar",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:59:00.383Z"),
    "question" : "What is the typical career progression at Deloitte? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603631860c817f0398fa2c33"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-data-science-a-more-stable-career-than-web-development?-",
    "answer" : "Chuong (Tom) Do, former Head of Data and Analytics at Coursera (2012-2017)Answered 3 years agoIs data science a more stable career than web development? Chuong (Tom) Do Personally, I believe that data science offers fantastic opportunities for career growth for a couple reasons: Market demand. The market demand for data science is certainly huge and unlikely to go away any time soon. At the core of this is the fact that data science is difficult (top data scientists are an extremely rare breed) yet generates enormous value when done well.Skill development. Effective data science is extremely cross-disciplinary (computer science, statistics, machine learning, business, science) and requires a balance of hard technical and soft communication skills. In practice, this means that a data scientist has the flexibility to develop a well-rounded skill set or specialize more narrowly based on his/her preferences. For example, on different days, you might be workingContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:59:18.463Z"),
    "question" : "Is data science a more stable career than web development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603631970c817f0398fa2c37"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-career-growth-in-web-development?-",
    "answer" : "I have been earning a living as a programmer for over 50 years, and I have seen things develop and then blossom. Web development was like that. The initial web pages were pretty much boring lines of monospace text since browsers didn’t support multiple fonts. Links were only a word or a statement that was highlighted, sometimes with only an underline. HTML was primitive, browsers were primitive, and CSS did not yet exist, nor did JavaScript. So, I guess you can say I just watched it happen, and wrote a bit of web code myself.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:59:35.148Z"),
    "question" : "How is career growth in web development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603631a90c817f0398fa2c3f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-make-my-career-in-Google-as-a-Java-software-developer?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T10:59:53.371Z"),
    "question" : "How can I make my career in Google as a Java software developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603631cf0c817f0398fa2c85"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-becoming-a-web-developer-a-good-career-choice-in-2018?-",
    "answer" : "It’s a great career. It’s not for everyone and there are some tedious points but if you enjoy solving challenging problems and programming you will likely enjoy it.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:00:31.691Z"),
    "question" : "Is becoming a web developer a good career choice in 2018? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603631f70c817f0398fa2cc9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-skills-do-I-need-to-develop-for-a-career-in-Business-Intelligence-and-Data-warehousing?-",
    "answer" : "Nowadays Business Intelligence opens opportunities to many fields as far as career prospects are concerned. If you are looking to develop a career as a SQL or BI developer, then I would suggest to develop skill-sets on SQL Querying, Data Modelling and atleast get a basic understanding on how different reporting tools interact. If you are an absolute beginner and want to start learning SQL - I have a few free courses on my Website or Udemy Page BI analyst roles require you to have solid understanding of the business, good verbal communication skills and the ability to tell a story using good visualization and reporting skills. Tableau, QlikView, SSRS etc. are some of the commonly used tools for reporting purposes. BI / Data Science roles require you to have good understanding of Statistical a Continue Reading Nowadays Business Intelligence opens opportunities to many fields as far as career prospects are concerned. If you are looking to develop a career as a SQL or BI developer, then I would suggest to develop skill-sets on SQL Querying, Data Modelling and atleast get a basic understanding on how different reporting tools interact. If you are an absolute beginner and want to start learning SQL - I have a few free courses on my Website or Udemy Page BI analyst roles require you to have solid understanding of the business, good verbal communication skills and the ability to tell a story using good visualization and reporting skills. Tableau, QlikView, SSRS etc. are some of the commonly used tools for reporting purposes. BI / Data Science roles require you to have good understanding of Statistical a Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:01:11.437Z"),
    "question" : "What skills do I need to develop for a career in Business Intelligence and Data warehousing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036320c0c817f0398fa2ccf"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-of-a-Web-Developer?-Is-it-a-good-career-path?-",
    "answer" : "I am inclined to answer that the future is bright for web developers. Not because I am clairvoyant but because I am naturally an optimist. Mind you, it isn’t always easy to be optimistic. I recently attended a workshop with the brilliant John Coyle who said, “today is the slowest day of the rest of your life”. The pace at which we are going to have to adapt to change is, admittedly, terrifying. But, here is the good news. The future is bright for those who can adapt, and web developers — the good ones anyway — are highly adaptive: We constantly have to refresh our skills.We continually learn new frameworks.Once we learn one programming language, we’ve proven to ourselves that we can pick up another one.We tend to be well informed, can anticipate trends, and can empower ourselves to take the Continue Reading I am inclined to answer that the future is bright for web developers. Not because I am clairvoyant but because I am naturally an optimist. Mind you, it isn’t always easy to be optimistic. I recently attended a workshop with the brilliant John Coyle who said, “today is the slowest day of the rest of your life”. The pace at which we are going to have to adapt to change is, admittedly, terrifying. But, here is the good news. The future is bright for those who can adapt, and web developers — the good ones anyway — are highly adaptive: We constantly have to refresh our skills.We continually learn new frameworks.Once we learn one programming language, we’ve proven to ourselves that we can pick up another one.We tend to be well informed, can anticipate trends, and can empower ourselves to take the Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:01:32.535Z"),
    "question" : "What is the future of web development in your opinion? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036321e0c817f0398fa2cd7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-Infosys-DC-in-India-is-best-in-terms-of-career-development?-",
    "answer" : "Chiraj Mhase Now that I have been in Infosys for more than a year and that to in 3 different locations ,according to me the best location from career point of view is hands down CHENNAI!! If you see, every so called south indian state has its own DC. Chennai(tamilnadu) , trivandrum(kerala) , hyderabad and karnataka has 2; bangalore and mysore. Statistically  speaking , every south indian individual would like to be in his own state!   Chandigarh DC is the smallest of all, that leaves only one option for north indians i.e pune mainly coz of the eating habits . So every infosion from maharashtra and above wants pune. People dont prefer chennai coz of the humid environment. Less strength(10k) more project opportunities, more onsite opportunities. I was in chennai but then got myself transferred to pune  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:01:50.333Z"),
    "question" : "Which Infosys DC in India is best in terms of career development? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036322f0c817f0398fa2cde"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-path-of-a-software-developer-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Yogesh Yadu I would not say to try this one that one and your life will be better in software development area. First of all you should ask yourself whether you are interested in software development field or not. If you are having a interest in software development area and you are enough capable then 7 figure salary is waiting for you irrespective of your years of experience in IT firm . U won't buy it right ? In India there are having IT firms , which pays 7 figure salary like Amazon , Facebook , Microsoft , TIAA, Google etc . Ohhh good to know , but how to get a chance to have an interview with these firms ? Right ? Make good connection with HRs of those big companies through LinkedIn. So that they can refer you for an interview .There are having lots of websites which provides online programming competContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:02:07.721Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career path of a software developer in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603632410c817f0398fa2d19"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-typical-career-path-of-Android-developer-in-comparison-with-the-traditional-developers?-",
    "answer" : "As  Android provides an interesting revenue model, a lot of organizations  have a dedicated team for application development with hiring catching  pace. The unique advantage of learning app development is that learners  can choose to work or freelance. Similarly, once that person masters  developing apps through Android it becomes easy to develop apps for  other operating systems! The graph below is just an assumption of a person having knowledge of Java and where he/she could go from there.  Here it  clearly shows that application development is one of the promising  career paths for professionals who just love creating apps. In comparison to other technology developers, the future of an Android developer is brighter. It has many reasons. One of them is, uses of Android based smartphones are expanding with leaps and bounds. And, in future also it will keep expanding. It is because of the cheap device cost and open source nature of the Android programming. Google Play Store– The Huge App MarketEvery  since Google rolled out its play store, the joy of experiencing app has  only multiplied tenfold. There was a time when we all looked up to the  iTunes store from Apple and sometimes getting an iphone was nearly  impossible. But with the Google play store and Android smartphones  access to apps has become so easy for all.Let’s look at some numbers… Android is the primary OS for 300 Smartphones, 90 Tablets & 6 E-ReadersEveryday around 1.5 million Android devices are activated across the globe.There are over 1,460,800 apps in Google Play store & growing!Over 60% of Android apps are for free!Penetration on Different devicesAndroid  is everywhere. Let’s face it. Recently, the Moto 360 got launched to  compete with Apple Smartwatch and then there is the Google glass powered  by the Android operating system. Staggeringly, the total number of  Android devices sold is 1,175,450,000! Some of the devices supported include Smart TVs, Smartphones, Tablets, Portable Media Players, Camera, VoIP Phones, Video game player, Car DVD Player, Car Systems, Smartwatches and even Drones. What’s in for the developer?It’s  simple. Different devices offer different opportunities! Smart TV  customers for example will have different expectation than Smartphone  users when it comes to apps. Taking cue from this small insight, app  developers can launch apps for each type of customer segment thereby  widening their base and increasing their revenue many times. The bottom line, being an Android application developer is a safe bet in terms of career prospect. Courtesy: edureka.co",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:02:25.788Z"),
    "question" : "What is the typical career path of Android developer in comparison with the traditional developers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603632560c817f0398fa2d22"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-scope-of-MEAN-stack-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Most associations are near the precarious edge of utilizing Mean Stack Development for creating web applications. As its fundamental design is based on java-script advances. It utilizes a similar code for the customer just as on the worker side. Because of this trademark, it is a straightforward language and saves time in web application development. Node just causes it to chip away at the Linux working framework. Just as in the Windows working framework additionally permits the engineer to distribute the application straightforwardly to the worker. The MongoDB information base is anything but difficult to make, where the client can undoubtedly bring, alter, or erase the information, which prompts the fast improvement of the application. Because of its quick, basic, and convenient nature for  Continue Reading Most associations are near the precarious edge of utilizing Mean Stack Development for creating web applications. As its fundamental design is based on java-script advances. It utilizes a similar code for the customer just as on the worker side. Because of this trademark, it is a straightforward language and saves time in web application development. Node just causes it to chip away at the Linux working framework. Just as in the Windows working framework additionally permits the engineer to distribute the application straightforwardly to the worker. The MongoDB information base is anything but difficult to make, where the client can undoubtedly bring, alter, or erase the information, which prompts the fast improvement of the application. Because of its quick, basic, and convenient nature for  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:02:46.564Z"),
    "question" : "What is the future scope of MEAN stack developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603632670c817f0398fa2d29"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-would-be-a-proactive-approach-to-a-software-development-career-looking-out-to-2025-or-2035?-",
    "answer" : "Jeff House Take challenging jobs, do what it takes to succeed and learn.   Especially learn. I'm going to go out on a limb here and talk about something I've been thinking about this for quite some time now: especially given how much need there is for software developers, and how few truly good developers there are, I think we're going to start moving toward a world where software writes more of our software for us.    I'm not talking about AI, and I don't mean that they'll necessarily \"generate code\", but that systems will further abstract away some of the common, boring elements (why do I still have to think about where my data is?   I probably won't have to in 20 years.   Will I use a web framework?  Or will we even consider the display and let the receiving device handle it according to requirement Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:03:03.848Z"),
    "question" : "What would be a proactive approach to a software development career looking out to 2025 or 2035? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036327c0c817f0398fa2d65"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-transition-from-software-tester-to-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I transition from software tester to developer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:03:24.229Z"),
    "question" : "How do I transition from software tester to developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603632af0c817f0398fa2dab"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-ladder-of-a-BizTalk-developer?-",
    "answer" : "BizTalk is still most widely used middle ware Enterprise application integration platform. Since it’s a Microsoft Product for Integration so it’s understood that why it is most popular among other middleware systems. BizTalk has a great scope in future since its been used almost by 81% fortune 100 companies and many other government organizations are also using BizTalk for Integrating data. Career Ladder- Trainee BizTalk Developer(0–1 year)(Primarily involved in support)BizTalk Developer(2–3 years) (Involved in Minor and major change request and projects including admin and support part as well)Senior BizTalk Developer/BizTalk Consultant (3–5 Years)- Works with a team of number of people and acts accordingly on a project’s requirements.Team Lead(BizTalk)(5–7 years)- Works as a Team Lead by hContinue Reading BizTalk is still most widely used middle ware Enterprise application integration platform. Since it’s a Microsoft Product for Integration so it’s understood that why it is most popular among other middleware systems. BizTalk has a great scope in future since its been used almost by 81% fortune 100 companies and many other government organizations are also using BizTalk for Integrating data. Career Ladder- Trainee BizTalk Developer(0–1 year)(Primarily involved in support)BizTalk Developer(2–3 years) (Involved in Minor and major change request and projects including admin and support part as well)Senior BizTalk Developer/BizTalk Consultant (3–5 Years)- Works with a team of number of people and acts accordingly on a project’s requirements.Team Lead(BizTalk)(5–7 years)- Works as a Team Lead by hContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:04:15.125Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career ladder of a BizTalk developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603632c70c817f0398fa2db2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Silicon-Valley-truly-the-best-place-to-start-a-career-as-a-software-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Bruce Lin",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:04:39.183Z"),
    "question" : "Is Silicon Valley truly the best place to start a career as a software developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603632da0c817f0398fa2dba"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Android-app-development-a-saturated-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Benny Alexander 5",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:04:58.065Z"),
    "question" : "Is Android app development a saturated career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603632fe0c817f0398fa2dff"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-alternate-careers-for-a-software-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the alternate careers for a software developer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:05:34.584Z"),
    "question" : "What are the alternate careers for a software developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603633120c817f0398fa2e07"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-software-development-a-good-career-for-me?-",
    "answer" : "There is almost certainly a place for you in the software ecosystem. To help find it, first consider what attracted you to software engineering. Software engineering can be very analytical, solitary, and focused (with breaks of great collaboration). But there are many related areas which are in demand. For example: If you prefer primarily to collaborate, communicate, plan, and help to resolve issues (and, um, attend a LOT of meetings), then project manager might be a good role for you.If you like technical aspects of programming but don’t want to be as solitary and deeply analytical, then test automation is a great skill to develop. Always in demand.Finally, you can pick from a spectrum of other areas, e.g., human factors, database design/admin, dev ops, security, support, or system adminisContinue Reading There is almost certainly a place for you in the software ecosystem. To help find it, first consider what attracted you to software engineering. Software engineering can be very analytical, solitary, and focused (with breaks of great collaboration). But there are many related areas which are in demand. For example: If you prefer primarily to collaborate, communicate, plan, and help to resolve issues (and, um, attend a LOT of meetings), then project manager might be a good role for you.If you like technical aspects of programming but don’t want to be as solitary and deeply analytical, then test automation is a great skill to develop. Always in demand.Finally, you can pick from a spectrum of other areas, e.g., human factors, database design/admin, dev ops, security, support, or system adminisContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:05:54.884Z"),
    "question" : "Is software development a good career for me? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603633260c817f0398fa2e44"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-careers-after-quitting-as-PHP-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Even after quitting as php developer you are still a developer unless you dropped the idea of doing programming, I assumed that you have prepared in some other language you can switch on to that or take some entirely new field. Still you might have ample knowledge of frontend and backend at this stage so you can opt for more specialize role may be a html developer, javascript developer or dba.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:06:14.196Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best careers after quitting as PHP developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603633380c817f0398fa2e4a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-natural-career-path-for-software-developers?-",
    "answer" : "There is no single path, no single time change horizon. It all depends on how your passion evolves. For some people, they failed their first computer science class and they never became a software developer. For some, they graduated during the tech bubble bust and chose a non-tech job. For some, they got tired of the tech after worked for a few years and transitioned themselves out of tech and became a tax preparation agent, a real estate agent, or started a non-tech small business. For some, they went to a business school in their late twenties or early thirties and never transitioned out of their tech positions because either their tech jobs paid more or it was too hard to transition to a new role/function with limited experience. Lucky ones were able to transition into project managers, Continue Reading There is no single path, no single time change horizon. It all depends on how your passion evolves. For some people, they failed their first computer science class and they never became a software developer. For some, they graduated during the tech bubble bust and chose a non-tech job. For some, they got tired of the tech after worked for a few years and transitioned themselves out of tech and became a tax preparation agent, a real estate agent, or started a non-tech small business. For some, they went to a business school in their late twenties or early thirties and never transitioned out of their tech positions because either their tech jobs paid more or it was too hard to transition to a new role/function with limited experience. Lucky ones were able to transition into project managers, Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:06:32.829Z"),
    "question" : "What is the natural career path for software developers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603633490c817f0398fa2e52"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-should-I-start-career-as-a-freelancer-software-and-web-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Personally I don`t think that having only 6 months experience you could be better freelancer, but however I am trying such way to reach there. 1. Identify your key skills. Before getting started as a freelancer, this is the most important thing to do. Identify the skills which you are already great at. Now this might sound a bit obvious but identifying a skill set which lets you stand out form the crowd helps you go get the initial projects. So take a pen and paper and list out all the possible skills you have, for example web-development, mobile application development etc. The next task is to find out a single skill in which you are most good at. 2. Selecting a platform.Selecting a platform is the next most important thing when it comes to starting your freelancing career. You must make sur Continue Reading Personally I don`t think that having only 6 months experience you could be better freelancer, but however I am trying such way to reach there. 1. Identify your key skills. Before getting started as a freelancer, this is the most important thing to do. Identify the skills which you are already great at. Now this might sound a bit obvious but identifying a skill set which lets you stand out form the crowd helps you go get the initial projects. So take a pen and paper and list out all the possible skills you have, for example web-development, mobile application development etc. The next task is to find out a single skill in which you are most good at. 2. Selecting a platform.Selecting a platform is the next most important thing when it comes to starting your freelancing career. You must make sur Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:06:49.429Z"),
    "question" : "How should I start career as a freelancer software and web developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036335d0c817f0398fa2e5c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-it-like-to-be-an-AI-developer?-",
    "answer" : "As we know Artificial Intelligence has picked the app development industry by storm and the need for skilled AI developers is on a rise. But, what it is to be an AI developer?  As we try to understand Artificial Intelligence development, an AI developer is someone who constantly plays two roles – • He researches the various advancements in the field of artificial intelligence and machine learning to bring them into development. • He understands and analyse the custom requirements of various clients to bring their concept of AI applications to life. Various Important Roles of an AI developer AI or machine learning researcher: An AI developer has to constantly research the modifications and additions in the world of machine learning and changes in the algorithm on which the artificial intelligence Continue Reading As we know Artificial Intelligence has picked the app development industry by storm and the need for skilled AI developers is on a rise. But, what it is to be an AI developer?  As we try to understand Artificial Intelligence development, an AI developer is someone who constantly plays two roles – • He researches the various advancements in the field of artificial intelligence and machine learning to bring them into development. • He understands and analyse the custom requirements of various clients to bring their concept of AI applications to life. Various Important Roles of an AI developer AI or machine learning researcher: An AI developer has to constantly research the modifications and additions in the world of machine learning and changes in the algorithm on which the artificial intelligence Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:07:09.368Z"),
    "question" : "What is it like to be an AI developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036336e0c817f0398fa2e96"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-career-choices-after-3-years-of-software-development-experience-in-the-IT-industry?-",
    "answer" : "Well personal choices may vary, but broadly there are two choices if you to want to continue in IT industry: Aim for becoming an Architect: Go in depth - Work on your technical skills. You need to do justice with the experience you earn in this industry. Learn as much as possible about app, web & backend(Database Design). Keep your self updated about emerging trends.Aim for becoming a Manager: Broaden - Project planning, risk forecast, learn leadership traits , how to interact with people, improve your communication skill. This does not mean you do not require technical skills.As per your experience 3 years - your next target should be sharpen your specialized skill & be aware of emerging trends & to become Module lead / Team lead in next 2–3 years. It is upto you to choose your path after  Continue Reading Well personal choices may vary, but broadly there are two choices if you to want to continue in IT industry: Aim for becoming an Architect: Go in depth - Work on your technical skills. You need to do justice with the experience you earn in this industry. Learn as much as possible about app, web & backend(Database Design). Keep your self updated about emerging trends.Aim for becoming a Manager: Broaden - Project planning, risk forecast, learn leadership traits , how to interact with people, improve your communication skill. This does not mean you do not require technical skills.As per your experience 3 years - your next target should be sharpen your specialized skill & be aware of emerging trends & to become Module lead / Team lead in next 2–3 years. It is upto you to choose your path after  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:07:26.432Z"),
    "question" : "What are career choices after 3 years of software development experience in the IT industry? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603633820c817f0398fa2e9e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-an-exhaustive-list-of-skills-I-need-to-have-to-be-a-web-developer?-",
    "answer" : "Gareth McCumskey I had no desire to answer this question, but then I saw a few terrible answers being given and had to set the record straight. (So if my answer confuses you, please refer to other answers to see the misinformation that I am firing at.) You want to be a web developer? Here’s what I know about being a professional front-end developer. First off, you need to know that a web developer is not a web designer. So, no, Photoshop is not required for you to be a web developer. Developers write code, designers design. Furthermore, in 2017 there are preferred alternatives to Photoshop if you’re a web designer. Second, all you really need to focus on is JavaScript. Everything else is a branch of JavaScript that you will figure out through learning JavaScript. Except CSS, of course, but there’s no CSS issue Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T11:07:46.312Z"),
    "question" : "What is an exhaustive list of skills I need to have to be a web developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}